<planetinfos>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>0</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Citadel</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Supposedly constructed by the long-extinct Protheans, this colossal deep-space station serves as the capital of the Citadel Council. Gravity is simulated through rotation, and is a comfortable 1.02 standard Gs on the Wards and a light 0.3 standard Gs on the Presidium Ring. (Small sections of graffiti have been found in station sub-structures, suggesting that perhaps the Protheans were not responsible for the bulk of construction. Bemused maintenance workers report that the graffiti is often a variation of ‘Keeper #13489317498813789 was here.’)

      TRAVEL ADVISORY: Due to new Citadel regulations, ‘down the shaft’ is no longer an acceptable vector when speaking with Traffic Control. There are also no fish in the Presidium.

      TRAVEL ADVISORY: Elevators to and from the Presidium are currently experiencing issues and are operating at minimum speeds; please plan accordingly. If you are in need of urgent transportation, please use the Citadel shuttles or the stairs.

      Total Length (Open): 44.7 km
      Diameter (Open): 12.8 km
      Population:  13.2 million (not including keepers)
      Gross Weight: 7.11 billion metric tons
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Citadel</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>1</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>*Placeholder*</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>*Placeholder*</PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Error</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>2</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Mercury</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Initial exploration on Mercury was limited by the planet's proximity to the sun. However, a probe sent into the atmosphere transmitted images of development on the surface. Most were of blocky, unremarkable ruins. However, a large triangular super-structure was clearly visible in one of the images. Later attempts at investigation were unsuccessful, as the probes simply disappeared upon contact with the super-structure. Several solar power stations were eventually established. All but a few seem to have collapsed into the mass of blocks and rubble.

      Population: 340

      Orbital Distance: 0.39 AU
      Orbital Period: 88 Earth Days
      Radius: 2440 km
      Day Length: 58.7 Earth Days
      Atmospheric Pressure: Trace
      Surface Temperature: 430 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.38 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Mercury</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>3</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Venus</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Due to the inhospitable atmosphere, development on Venus has been limited to research facilities. A small company known as Au Raa holds most of the rights to the planet. Information on this company is not available to the general public. As such, the nature of their research facilities is a topic of much speculation, with the most popular rumors involving manipulation of the human genome. However, this cannot be substantiated and the sulphuric atmosphere of the planet deters any long-range scanning from curious eyes.

      Population: 800

      Orbital Distance: 0.72 AU
      Orbital Period: 224.7 Earth Days
      Radius: 6052 km
      Day Length: 243 Earth Days
      Atmospheric Pressure: 90 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 465 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.88 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Venus</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>4</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Earth</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      For detailed information, please refer to the standard issue Alliance Galactic Codex. Please note: the section regarding ‘Flat Earth and You’ is no longer up to date, as it was discovered just last year that the planet is not, in fact, a giant disc supported by four elephants and floating through space on the back of a giant turtle.

      Population (Surface): 11.4 billion
      Population (L4 and L5 stations): 250,000

      Orbital Distance: 1 AU
      Orbital Period: 1 Earth Years
      Radius: 6378 km
      Day Length: 23.9 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 23 Celsius
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Earth</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>5</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Mars</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Mars was once the future hope of humanity, as wars and resource shortages made life on Earth ever more untenable. However, the first scientific teams sent to the planet discovered that terraforming on a massive scale had turned the planet into an unstable warren of tunnels, inhabited by a massive worm. Carvings found in caves on the surface suggest that the as-yet unknown inhabitants of the planet may have formed a cult, worshipping this worm as their god.

      Colony Founded: 2103
      Population: 3.4 million
      Capital: Lowell City

      Orbital Distance: 1.52 AU
      Orbital Period: 1.88 Earth Years
      Radius: 3402 km
      Day Length: 24.6 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.06 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -138 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.38 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Mars</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>6</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Jupiter</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Jupiter's deep gravity well and lethal radiation have prevented any significant exploration of the planet. Some of the moons have been developed, with the largest outpost belonging to SST Laboratories, located on Ganymede. Most commonly associated with their Siege Automatons, the company has fallen out of favor in recent years due to Automaton usage in a major Earth crisis. Several abandoned B73 models can be seen littering the upper atmosphere of the moon.

      Population (all moons): 9100

      Orbital Distance: 5.2 AU
      Orbital Period: 11.7 Earth Years
      Radius: 71,492 km
      Day Length: 9.93 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Jupiter</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>7</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Saturn</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Saturn has been a major source of helium-3 fuel for fusion plants since the 2150s. The moon of Titan is mined for hydrocarbons and used as a hostile environment training facility for Alliance Marines. The rings of Saturn are littered with shredded ship remains, as competitive racing along the rings has proliferated.

      Population (orbitals and Titan): 117,000
      Capital: Huygens Dome

      Orbital Distance: 9.5 AU
      Orbital Period: 29.5 Earth Years
      Radius: 60,268 km
      Day Length: 10.3 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Saturn</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>8</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Uranus</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      After the development of mass effect FTL drives, distant Uranus was the target of a "land rush" to exploit its combination of plentiful helium-3 fuel and relatively shallow gravity well. Today, Uranus is the largest producer of He-3 in Alliance space. Probing is the most common way to extract gas and other useful resources from the gas giant’s exterior, but some deep investigative vessels have also attempted to extract denser gases from further within the planet. Most attempts have proven unsuccessful, as commercial-grade fuel tanks are unable to sustain the pressure and the result is a blow-out.

      Population: 371,000
      Capital: Sakharov Station

      Orbital Distance: 19.2 AU
      Orbital Period: 121.1 Earth Years
      Radius: 25,559 km
      Day Length: 17.3 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Uranus</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>9</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Neptune</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Neptune is an advanced training facility for combat operations. While used heavily by the Alliance, it is a commercial offering, permitting training for both military and non-military personnel. Through the use of cutting-edge simulation technology, training can be done to a very high degree of realism with low potential psychological impact on the participants in the event of a catastrophic failure.

      Their most famous simulation takes place in a crashed subway station, aptly named Firebase Neptune. This simulation is designed to improve the participants’ resistance to optical attacks on the battlefield by utilizing purple and white squares to represent walls and ceilings. Viewers of this simulation often call this effect "Eyebleed".

      Population (Triton): 70

      Orbital Distance: 29.1 AU
      Orbital Period: 164.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 24,764 km
      Day Length: 16.1 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Neptune</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>10</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Pluto</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Pluto is the gravitational "anchor" for the Prothean mass relay to Arcturus. Pluto and the Charon Relay (formerly encased in ice, and considered a moon) orbit each other. Pluto was stripped of its planetary status in the year 2006 after leading scientists on the system’s capital planet, Earth, started betting on an ancient sports game known as "curling". Leaders from multiple countries disagreed with the decision, but were unable to change course as the lead scientists of space at the time were bound by their bet. Today, Pluto is little more than a staging ground for the Charon Mass Relay.

      Population (gateway stations): 9300

      Orbital Distance: 39.5 AU
      Orbital Period: 247.7 Earth Years
      Radius: 1151 km
      Day Length: 9.4 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: Trace
      Surface Temperature: -229 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.06 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Pluto</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>11</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Luna</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      An early source of helium-3, Luna is now mined for materials used in space habitat construction. A folk legend from before space travel in the Sol system once described Luna as being made of cheese; exactly which kind has been debated widely among the population of Earth.

      While it has long been proven that Luna is not, in fact, made out of cheese, Neil Armstrong - the first human to step foot on Luna - is said to have thrown a wheel of cheese out of his landing craft upon first touchdown in 1969 to commemorate this legend. Even though the wheel has never been recovered, it is thought to be of the gouda variety. When asked why he chose this type, Neil supposedly replied with, "It is simply the best kind of cheese".

      Colony Founded: 2069
      Population: 4.1 million
      Capital: Armstrong

      Orbital Distance:  384,403 km (from Earth)
      Orbital Period: 27.3 Earth Days
      Radius: 1737 km
      Day Length: 27.3 Earth Days
      Atmospheric Pressure: Trace
      Surface Temperature: -53 Celsius
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Luna</ImageGroup>
    <ButtonLabel>Go exploring</ButtonLabel>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>12</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Corporate investment of the asteroid belt is at an all-time high due to discovery of a new element, adamantium. Considered one of the hardest minerals known to the galaxy, mining it has proved elusive for even the most powerful explosives. Some asteroids have been hauled away to be used directly as projectiles in space warfare by various species.

      Orbital Distance: 1.8 to 4.5 AU
      Population: 11,000
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>13</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Eden Prime</PlanetName>
    <PlanetName2>Dorstonis</PlanetName2>
    <PlanetDescription>
      This pastoral world marks the founding of the first Earth colony beyond a mass relay. The biosphere, though slightly thin, is well-suited to both humans and native Earth species. The original Systems Alliance colony was soon augmented by the arrival of corporate developments.

      Most notable of these was Ondore Lhusu’s discovery of the magicite mines, now a major export and source of revenue. The bulk of the development on %PLANETNAME% is still primarily agricultural, however, and the rolling green hills would not look out of place on Earth.

      Colony Founded: 2152
      Population: 3.7 million
      Capital: Bhujerba

      Orbital Period: 2.5 Earth Years
      Radius: 7026 km
      Day Length: 64.1 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.45 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 23 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.04 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Farm</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>14</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Neo Arcadia</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A hostile and closed-off planet, Neo Arcadia was once a world filled with lush forests and deep blue oceans. Technology use on Neo Arcadia advanced too rapidly for sustainability, eventually plunging the world into multiple devastating wars spanning hundreds of years.

      Today Neo Arcadia is the name of the capital city, the only remaining hospitable place on the planet. Facing an energy crisis that will cripple their remaining technologies, the leadership is embroiled in a civil war with a resistance force that is attempting to solve the energy crisis on its own.

      Orbital Period: 0.6 Earth Years
      Radius: 10893 km
      Day Length: 25.6 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 16.17 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 358 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 5.0 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>DestroyedWorld</ImageGroup>
    <NotPlayable>true</NotPlayable>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>15</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Corneria</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Corneria, the fourth planet of the %SYSTEMNAME% system, is an Earth-like terrestrial world primarily used for farming. It is the most populated planet in the system, with the majority of the population living in the mountain ranges that have rich soils for farming.

      The capital city has been besieged multiple times in recent years as several parties from opposing political factions have attempted to conquer the planet.

      Population: 2.2 Billion

      Orbital Period: 52.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 74,333 km
      Day Length: 10.5 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Farm</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>16</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Titania</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Millions of years ago, Titania was a beautiful planet with a thriving ecosystem full of intelligent, non-space-faring life. A meteor impact with the planet reduced the paradise world to the arid desert it can be seen as today. Asari scientific expeditions have found remains of a civilization from some of the ancient races; however, most intact pieces are thought to be buried deep under layers of ancient ash.

      Orbital Period:	129.9 Earth Years
      Radius: 3212 km
      Day Length: 63.9 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.02 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -203 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.2 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Desert</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>17</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Venom</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A world once considered a possible golden planet, Venom now serves as a reminder of the dangers involved in terraforming uncharted worlds. Decades ago during an advanced terraforming experiment, multiple catastrophic events chained into one other, turning plans for a new paradise world into an evacuation.

      Venom’s oceans are now highly acidic, toxic to all but the most hardy of creatures. The majority of the planet’s surface is in low light or complete darkness due to a constant thin layer of toxic smog in the atmosphere, which also killed off most surface-dwelling organisms.

      Venom now acts as a popular death-trap world, where all who are unfortunate enough to be stranded are doomed to die a painful death.

      Known surviving population: 1
      Orbital Period: 1029.9 Earth Years
      Radius 3730 km
      Day Length: 69.8 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.19 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -216 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.3 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    `	<ImageGroup>SeaFloor</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>18</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Noveria</PlanetName>
    <PlanetName2>Grunty Industries</PlanetName2>
    <PlanetDescription>
      %PLANETNAME% is a small, frozen, terrestrial world, barely habitable by conventional definitions. It is privately run by the %PLANETNAME% Development Corporation, which controls the production facilities that cover the planet. Due to the significant overcrowding of factories, pollution is widespread, with some factories even surrounded by toxic moats.

      Secret investigations into the factories have surfaced pictures of incredibly dangerous working conditions, including multiple broken windows going unrepaired, an open elevator shaft that several workers have died in, and a sentient blowtorch that lives in the basement of one of the facilities.

      Colony Founded: 2000
      Population: 2,200
      Planetary leader: Gruntilda Winkybunion

      Orbital Distance: 0.9 AU
      Orbital Period: 0.9 Earth Years
      Radius: 5656 km
      Day Length: 52.0 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.87 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -1 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.81
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Factory</ImageGroup>
    <ButtonLabel>Put on boots</ButtonLabel>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>19</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Arrakis</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Arrakis has constant wind storms blowing across the surface due to its planetary tilt. Millenia of windstorms have eroded the surface crust down to a fine dust, which is carried around the planet on a near-constant basis. With only trace amounts of natural precipitation, colonization attempts have proven to be tough for nearly all races, leaving Arrakis as a quiet, oft-forgotten world.

      Orbital Period: 0.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 32,285 km
      Day Length: 13.4 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Desert</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>20</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Outset</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Outset is a water world, with over 99% of its surface covered in ocean. Many small islands near the equator mark the only habitable areas for terrestrial life. Orbital scans show several underwater anomalies, but without further investigation, these items remain a mystery.

      Orbital Distance: 6.3 AU
      Orbital Period: 17.7 Earth Years
      Radius: 1089 km
      Day Length: 17.7 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.1 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 20 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.89 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Ocean</ImageGroup>
    <ButtonLabel>Get sunglasses</ButtonLabel>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>21</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Oswald</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Oswald is a private world, with little known about the planetside business conducted by its owner, Binary Helix. Named after an invention of the original corporation’s founder in the 1900s, Oswald is a quiet world. Orbital scans show multiple planetary defense installations on at least six different regions of the planet.

      Orbital Distance: 24.5 AU
      Orbital Period: 136.3 Earth Years
      Radius: 7547 km
      Day Length: 62.0 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.07 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -220 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.7 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Sky</ImageGroup>
    <NotPlayable>true</NotPlayable>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>22</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Tallon IV</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Fifty-one years ago, Tallon IV was impacted by a small meteorite that crashed into the northern hemisphere of the planet. In the years that followed, mutations of the local wildlife have rapidly increased, with the planet’s wildlife becoming increasingly hostile to visitors. Scientific instruments on the surface of the planet indicate a large radioactive energy source at the planet’s core, which has been steadily increasing over time.

      Orbital Period: 97.3 Earth Years
      Radius: 5756 km
      Day Length: 21.8 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.79 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 28 Celsius
      Surface Gravity:  0.97 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Wilderness</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>23</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Aether</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Aether is a rogue planet in the %SYSTEMNAME% system, home to the Luminoth. Fifty years ago, a meteorite crashed into Aether with unusual force, destroying the planet's natural beauty. Shortly after the impact, all communication to the planetary leadership was lost, and teams sent by the Citadel Council to investigate never returned. Orbital scans indicate there has been no recent planetside activity by intelligent species.

      WARNING: This planet has been marked as hostile to lifeforms by the Citadel Council. Landing on this planet is not permitted.

      Orbital Period: 5.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 4905 km
      Day Length: 55.2 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 2.1 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 24 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.8 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Wilderness</ImageGroup>
    <NotPlayable>true</NotPlayable>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>24</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Bespin</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Bespin is a standard hydrogen-helium gas giant with traces of ammonia. Hydrocarbons in the atmosphere lend it a distinct tint. Thousands of gas mining stations litter the high atmosphere.

      Orbital Period: 52.0 Earth Years
      Radius: 35,417 km
      Day Length: 14.7 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Sky</ImageGroup>
    <NotPlayable>true</NotPlayable>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>25</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Trevelyan</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Trevelyan is a lifeless rock with a thick, cloudy atmosphere. A glowing green "Jupiter spot" spins violently over the axis of the planet. A salarian religious cult claims that this spot is actually a breach between waking and dreaming worlds. Their teachings make many references to a Herald that will come and seal the rift forever.

      Orbital Period: 74.9 Earth Years
      Radius: 1163 km
      Day Length: 36.7 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.00 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -147 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.1 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Desert</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>26</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>true</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>MSV Kaldwin</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      The Kaldwin is a Kowloon-class modular conveyor of human design. The ship appears to have been torn apart from the inside by some kind of void. A glowing emblem can be seen on a piece of metal spinning through space. The Normandy’s scanners identify it only as "Mark of the Outsider".

      Registry: Private Owner, Captain Sokolov
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Ship</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>27</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Kass</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Kass’ atmosphere is tinted blue by trace quantities of methane. Deep crevasses criss-cross the surface, and a cheerfully eerie whistling noise can be heard when the wind blows across them.

      Orbital Period: 173.4 Earth Years
      Radius: 53,520 km
      Day Length: 15.5 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Wilderness</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>28</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Antoneese</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      When Antoneese was first discovered, orbital surveys showed remains of an extinct species. Further investigation found inscriptions detailing the last days of intelligent life on the planet, which showed that they were nearing the ability to reach low orbit.

      During a commemorative event, the leader of the dominant group of Antoneese told an ill-timed joke, which incensed opposing parties. In the following weeks, multiple escalations of hostility led to a war that enveloped the planet. The populations of Antoneese were devastated, leading to famine and a solar shield caused by the smoke from burning cities. Most, if not all, life on the planet died shortly after. The age of the texts detailing these events could not be reliably determined.

      Orbital Period: 12.0 Earth Years
      Radius: 6694 km
      Day Length: 59.7 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.19 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -16 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.16 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>DestroyedWorld</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>29</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Zeal</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Zeal is a frozen terrestrial planet with a near-absent atmosphere. Scans reveal the remnants of several orbiting bodies, possibly space stations, although they appear to be made of rock. Frozen pillars of ice tether several of these bodies to the surface of the planet.

      There is little information available about Zeal. A single asari text makes brief reference to "Lavos", an alien life form that allegedly landed millennia ago and proceeded to drain the energy of every living being on the planet. Though scientifically unlikely, "Schala et Janus" is still a popular read among mythology enthusiasts.

      Orbital Period: 2.4 Earth Years
      Radius: 7708 km
      Day Length: 33.2 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.03 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -150 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.1 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Ice</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>30</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Morte</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Morte is a frigid world with a thick nitrogen-argon atmosphere and several moons. The largest of these are Annah, Dak’kon, and Ignus.

      Experienced travelers more often refer to Morte as "Mortuary" due to the overlapping gravity wells between the planet and its moons. Ships trying to save fuel by flying between them are likely to find themselves dragged into orbit and ripped apart by opposing forces.

      Orbital Period: 31.4 Earth Years
      Radius: 5492 km
      Day Length: 69.0 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 17.11 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -134 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.7 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Ice</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>31</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Shiva</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A small, unmanned flyby probe provides the only available data for this tiny planet. It is composed almost completely of ice, with a trace atmosphere of krypton.

      Planetary maps indicate mass concentrations of carbon under intense pressure at the core of the planet. Normandy's more detailed survey suggests the core may solidify into something akin to diamond. The difficulty of extracting it, however, will likely deter any mining interest in the planet.

      Orbital Period: 82.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 3198 km
      Day Length: 32.5 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.03 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -237 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.2 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Ice</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>32</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Charybdis</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Though it is one of the oldest entries in the star charts, Charybdis has not yet been fully mapped. An immensely powerful magnetic field disrupts the electronics of all currently known ship designs, preventing most from getting too close to the planet.

      Due to this magnetic field, metallic particles in the range of the magnetic field form an even distribution around the planet, which significantly diminishes the usefulness of long-range visual surveys of the planet’s surface. In spite of these obstacles, the Salarian Special Tactics Group conducted long-range surveys over a period of two decades. Results from these surveys showed unknown life forms flying around on the planet, as well as near-constant lightning strikes in specific areas.

      The Salarians named this species "Ceph" and, while they are not yet space-faring, it is expected they will pose significant risk to galactic civilization once capable.

      Orbital Period: 94.0 Earth Years
      Radius: 4439 km
      Day Length: 46.9 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.88 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 127 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.85 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Generic</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>33</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Panchaea</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Panchaea is a small planet most notable for housing Sarif Industries’ main research outpost.  Its two moons, Hengsha and Belltower, are home to the original LIMB Clinics. These bioengineering facilities pioneered the first cybernetic augmentations available on the open market. Most of their products have since been eclipsed by asari equivalents. However, Sarif is still the main producer of Neuropozyne, an immunosuppressive drug that prevents augmentation rejection.

      Sarif has been heavily criticized by the Sirta Foundation in recent years, most notably for artificially reducing the supply of Neuropozyne.

      Orbital Period: 1.4 Earth Years
      Radius: 4384 km
      Day Length: 1.4 Earth Years
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.42 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 35 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.44 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Generic</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>34</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Gol Acheron</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Gol Acheron is a modestly-sized terrestrial planet. The native inhabitants are primitive and most live in small villages along the coast, guided by four sages. Anthropologists describe a culture passed down from an ancient race known only as the Precursors. Most of the planet’s economy and industry is based on the collection of an energy source simply referred to as "eco".

      Orbital Period: 25.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 3675 km
      Day Length: 57.0 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.37 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 41 Celsius
      Surface gravity: 0.39 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Generic</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>35</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Belias</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Belias is a blisteringly hot terrestrial planet with an iron-rich, rusty red surface. Its huge ranges of volcanoes are in a state of constant eruption and the atmosphere is choked with a thick cloud of ash.

      The Raithwall, a manned survey ship, met its end on Belias before it could finish mapping the system. The remnants of the ship have long been lost to the ever-shifting magma flow.

      Orbital Period: 3.3 Earth Years
      Radius: 6914 km
      Day Length: 33.4 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.48 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 497 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.88 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>LavaWorld</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>36</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Dantooine</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Dantooine is a relatively unremarkable planet covered mainly in flat grasslands. The ‘capital’ is nothing more than a scattered collection of small farms and the enclave of a reclusive monastic sect.

      Orbital Period: 239.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 78204 km
      Day Length: 10.0 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Generic</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>37</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>IF YOU SEE THIS PLEASE REPORT IT AS A BUG! IF YOU SEE THIS PLEASE REPORT IT AS A BUG!  IF YOU SEE THIS PLEASE REPORT IT AS A BUG!  IF YOU SEE THIS PLEASE REPORT IT AS A BUG!  IF YOU SEE THIS PLEASE REPORT IT AS A BUG!  IF YOU SEE THIS PLEASE REPORT IT AS A BUG! IF YOU SEE THIS PLEASE REPORT IT AS A BUG!  IF YOU SEE THIS PLEASE REPORT IT AS A BUG!  IF YOU SEE THIS PLEASE REPORT IT AS A BUG! Placeholder - some asteroids have null descriptions. Mgamerz, please fix to ensure the Bio2DA Cell is not null in the description column and ensure all asteroids have a enabled function index for opening</PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>38</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Xen</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Xen has a thin atmosphere of carbon dioxide and ethane, with surface temperatures hovering well below freezing. A massive hole has been blown into the side of the planet. A data dump from online backups of planetary development mark the site as the original location of Black Mesa Research Facility. The files make reference to an emergency event called a ‘resonance cascade’, but scientists brought in to study this event have still not worked out exactly what this means.

      Rival research facility Aperture Laboratories is on record with the simple statement "Good riddance. What a joke."

      Orbital Period: 21.4 Earth Years
      Radius: 5447 km
      Day Length: 37.2 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.58 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -35 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.86 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Barren</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>39</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Monokuma</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Monokuma is a terrestrial world with traces of several toxic gases in the atmosphere. It is tidally locked to its star, resulting in extreme cold temperatures on the permanently dark side of the planet. The light side is covered in what appears to be large salt flats, giving it an almost reflective appearance.

      Monokuma has a noticeable rift on the dark side of its upper quadrant. While the origins of the rift are still unknown, geological studies indicate that its steep reddish cliffs likely contain large amounts of precious metal. A small mining outpost was established on the rift’s outcropping, aptly named ‘Hope’s Peak’.

      Orbital Period: 2.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 1410 km
      Day Length 2.8 Earth Years
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.00 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 82 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.17 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Castle</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>40</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Nearrum</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Nearrum is a terrestrial world with a thin atmosphere of methane and argon. Its surface is mainly composed of basaltic rock. Its most prominent feature is the Farrum Rift, a long volcanic divergence zone that stretches across half of the northern hemisphere. The cliff surfaces are covered in massive circular fissures that appear artificially created, but their size makes this unlikely.

      Orbital Period: 6.3 Earth Years
      Radius: 6779 km
      Day Length: 31.7 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.67 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 58 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.82 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Generic</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>41</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Nirn</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Nirn is an icy terrestrial planet with a thin atmosphere of carbon dioxide and krypton. The planet’s mantle is hollow in most places and its surface is marred with holes large enough to see from space.

      Nirn’s underground cave systems support a surprisingly large variety of algaes and plankton, but the most notable is a small, weed-like root. This pale-green species gives off a faint glow that provides light enough for other fauna to grow. A red variety of the same root does not glow, but instead emits a faint, high-pitched chiming noise. The mechanism of the sound is still unknown, as the sample canister obtained by the original scientific exploration was noted on the manifest as ‘lost in accidental airlock cycling sequence’.

      Orbital Period: 35.4 Earth Years
      Radius: 3691 km
      Day Length: 61.7 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.27 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -84 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.28 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Ice</ImageGroup>
    <ButtonLabel>Go spelunking</ButtonLabel>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>42</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Anor Londo</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Anor Londo is a standard hydrogen-helium gas giant with a sodium atmosphere and one moon, Artorias.

      A striking formation of mineral spires is visible in the upper hemisphere. These spires catch the light during their brief time on the light side of the planet, taking on the appearance of a kindled bonfire.

      Orbital Period: 85.5 Earth Years
      Radius: 34,914 km
      Day Length: 11.5 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Sky</ImageGroup>
    <NotPlayable>true</NotPlayable>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>43</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>Asteroid belt description</PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>44</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <IsAsteroid>true</IsAsteroid>
    <PlanetName>Metallic Asteroid</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A metal-rich asteroid. There are multiple abandoned mining ships on the surface, with one of them fractured open to the vacuum of space.

      Radius: 94 km
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>45</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>true</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>MSV Toronto</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      The Toronto is a Kowloon-class modular conveyor of human design, configured for mixed freight and passenger hauling. There is a large ‘No. 1’ and what appears to be a maple leaf painted in blue on the side, possibly a reference to the city after which the conveyor was named. It is currently broadcasting garbled, vaguely insulting transmissions.

      Registry: Private Owner, Citadel Station
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Ship</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>46</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Wander</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Wander is a mostly oceanic planet with a few long, snaky islands. The largest of these is ringed by an insurmountable mountain range. Massive stone giants dot the landscape, sixteen in all, and appear to be vaguely animal in design. Their purpose is impossible to discern. A large stone bridge and a crumbling shrine indicate that this island must have been populated at one point, but no other traces of the former inhabitants remain.

      Orbital Distance: 5.6 AU
      Orbital Period: 3.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 42,418 km
      Day Length: 9.1 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Ocean</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>47</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Gaul</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Gaul is a small, verdant terrestrial world covered almost completely in forests and highlands. Its thin atmosphere is mostly made up of nitrogen with traces of oxygen. The conditions are not suitable for long-term human habitation. However, ambitious explorers can manage with simple, inexpensive survival gear.

      The Alliance Defense Data Network has records of several skirmishes over the planet. The most notable, known as the Siege of Alesia, saw the native inhabitants of the planet subjugated by ExoGeni militia forces.

      Orbital Distance: 69.9 AU
      Orbital Period: 102.0 Earth Years
      Radius: 4227 km
      Day Length: 102.0 Earth Years
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.36 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 1176 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.38 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Generic</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>48</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Installation 05</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Installation 05 is unique in that the name does not refer to the planet, but to the mechanical ring, or ‘halo’ that encircles it. Several expeditions have attempted to discover its origins and purpose, but all except one disappeared without a trace.

      A black box recovered from pieces of the Amber’s wreckage contains a garbled, audio-only recording of Commander Keyes repeating the word ‘Gravemind’.

      Orbital Period: 302.0 Earth Years
      Radius: 3742 km
      Day Length: 30.1 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.23 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 848 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.27
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>RingWorld</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>49</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>50</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <IsAsteroid>true</IsAsteroid>
    <PlanetName>Rocky Asteroid</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      This large asteroid has several smaller bodies orbiting it.
      Radius: 336 km
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>51</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>52</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Orb Ibanna</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Orb Ibanna is technically a terrestrial world; however, nearly all of the population lives in the mid-atmosphere above the cloud layer that surrounds the planet. With cities built atop towers that rise through the heavens, Orb Ibanna is a planet for the rich and elite of the galaxy.

      A popular gambling attraction on the planet is a dangerous race track, named Abyss, that connects the towers through tubes and race tracks. Racers pilot carts dragged behind large turbine engines at high speeds, which provide displays of spectacular reaction time, or - more commonly - explosive and guaranteed death.

      Orbital Distance: 3.7 AU
      Orbital Period: 1.02 Earth Years
      Radius: 8000 km
      Day Length: 31 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.76 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 11 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.7 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Sky</ImageGroup>
    <NotPlayable>true</NotPlayable>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>53</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Zavala</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      An enigmatic terrestrial planet, Zavala has an atmosphere of nitrogen and argon. It is blisteringly cold and a faint whitish haze can be seen rippling across its blue surface.

      Three times in the last century, ships stopping to discharge at nearby planets have reported geometric patterns of lights on the dark side of Zavala. Attempts at closer investigation could not be made, as an asteroid belt of whitish fragments surrounded the planet, and ship transponders were overridden with static-laced references to ‘the Traveler’.

      Orbital Distance: 2.0 AU
      Orbital Period: 2.1 Earth Years
      Radius: 5535 km
      Day Length: 53.8 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.5 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 166 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.7 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Ice</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>54</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Xenon</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Xenon features two large mountain ranges that form a cross near the equator of the planet, creating a large X that is visible from space. The mountain ranges are dotted with green fluorescent compounds, which allow them to be seen from space even on the dark side of the planet.

      Expeditions from various other planets often touch down on the surface, allowing galactic tourists to collect the fluorescent rocks as keepsakes.

      Orbital Period: 36.1 Earth Years
      Radius: 2236 km
      Day Length: 42.1 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.00 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -117 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.19 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Generic</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>55</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Atoli</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Atoli is small and pastoral with a lightly oxygenated atmosphere. The surface remains largely untouched. The equator is ringed with mesas, atop which a massive and ancient wall stands. The asari call the wall Morrigu Barrow, named for the ‘great gate of heaven’ often mentioned in their ancient legends. Along the length of the wall, unusual energy spores can be seen idly drifting through the air over the vast waterfalls that pour down from the mesas.

      Despite several attempts to send colony ships to the planet, the asari consider it a holy site and staunchly oppose any development efforts. Morrigu Barrow is nevertheless a popular destination for tourists of all kinds due to its rare beauty and unspoiled nature.

      Orbital Distance: 20.2 AU
      Orbital Period:2.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 11129 km
      Day Length: 23.6 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.29 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 12 Celsius
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Generic</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>56</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Charn</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Charn is a terrestrial planet in the throes of destruction. It orbits a red giant in the end stages of its life. The surface is cold and nearly dark. Great chasms cut through the land, their rivers long dried up. Scans show the sprawling ruins of cities built on a scale much larger than any of the galaxy’s currently known races.

      An Alliance probe passing through the system noted signs of geth activity. Ships are advised to avoid the system.

      Orbital Distance: 51.8 AU
      Orbital Period: 286.7 Earth Years
      Radius: 42,211 km
      Day Length: 12.8 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Ice</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>57</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>58</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Morganna</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Morganna is a massive whitish gas giant with eight moons. Originally named Epitaphs 1 through 8, the moons gained their more well-known names when quarian author Wielant circulated a poem called "Epitaph of Twilight" on the extranet. The poem, inspired by her Pilgrimage through the system, reimagined the moons as characters. Though the names were never officially changed, the poem gained widespread acclaim and most now refer to the moons as Skeith, Innis, Magus, Fidchell, Gorre, Macha, Tarvos, and Corbenik.

      Morganna’s gravitational pull has attracted Cubia, a ninth moon, into its orbit in recent years. Studies have revealed an unstable core, and Morganna’s pulsing gravitational waves will likely cause the new moon to shatter within the next decade.

      Orbital Period: 1.1 Earth Years
      Radius: 542489 km
      Day Length: 41.8 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 3.84 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 89 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 8.86 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Sky</ImageGroup>
    <NotPlayable>true</NotPlayable>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>59</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Valinor</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Valinor and its moon Melkor were spared only a cursory probe on initial exploration of the system, which reported a temperate planet with a moderate supply of light minerals. Alliance colonial surveyors two years later discovered that Melkor had succumbed to orbital decay and crashed into the surface of Valinor.

      Once a promising colony planet, Valinor is now scarred by a massive blast crater. Tsunamis stirred up by violent tectonic shifts have covered most of the surface in filthy ocean, and pieces of the shattered moon have rendered the remaining landmass completely unlivable.

      Orbital Period: 0.1 Earth Years
      Radius: 2147 km
      Day Length: 59.9 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.27 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 50 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.25 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>DestroyedWorld</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>60</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Firenze</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Firenze is a planet so small that many debate whether it should be reclassified as a moon. Its moderately high gravity, sandy surface, and tolerable extremes of temperature make it an ideal location for military training. The salarians maintain an official base of operations on the planet and on the two space stations in orbit around it.

      Despite the base’s status as an intake for rookie soldiers, rumors speculate that it may actually be a front to conceal the operations of a notoriously secretive STG cell known as the Assassins.

      Orbital Period: 7.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 22759 km
      Day Length: 13.7 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Generic</ImageGroup>
    <ButtonLabel>Infiltrate</ButtonLabel>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>61</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Bray</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Bray is a massive red planet with an unusually smooth surface. Sonar scans indicate the presence of a nearly hollow core. Ruined ships of failed expeditions still remain floating in low orbit, some of bearing the signs of an EMP attack, others crushed by unknown forces.

      A privately-funded scan of the planet from far above the atmosphere revealed a lattice of structures just beneath the surface, most notably a large pyramid at the center of the core. Despite several conspiracies arguing that the planet was created by a sentient ‘brain’, no other useful information has been discovered.

      Orbital Period: 20.4 Earth Years
      Radius: 74,221 km
      Day Length: 17.3 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>MarsGround</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>62</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Aen Elle</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Aen Elle is a planet steeped in legend, described in many ancient texts as a place of sublime beauty and advanced knowledge. Guided by these stories, an expedition of combined Council races was sent to track down Aen Elle’s whereabouts. The planet itself was eventually discovered in its accurate location. However, the intervening years had served to all but destroy the fabled paradise.

      Battered by a confluence with Eredin, a roving "ghost" planet, the planet is now overrun with virulent disease and grotesque creatures. Great swathes of the surface are encased in ice and the remaining atmosphere is heavy with frost. The skeletal ruins of once-graceful towers are the only remnant of its prior glory.

      Orbital Period: 37.5 Earth Years
      Radius: 10,314 km
      Day Length: 36.3 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.0 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -67 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.1 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Ice</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>63</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Nimona</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Nimona is a mid-sized terrestrial planet. Its characteristic deep pink color come from manganese-rich soil. The atmosphere consists mostly of chlorine, often condensing into bright green clouds.

      The planet is often nicknamed ‘the shapeshifter’ due to the ever-changing patterns of the cloud formations. Ships passing through the system will often capture images and upload them to a popular extranet gallery. The most well-known of these images shows a cloud formation that appears much like a dragon breathing fire.

      Orbital Period: 90.5 Earth Years
      Radius: 3686 km
      Day Length: 48.2 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.2 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -202 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.22 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Generic</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>64</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Virmire</PlanetName>
    <PlanetName2>Mandalore</PlanetName2>
    <PlanetDescription>
      %PLANETNAME% is a lush frontier world, covered in veshok forest, oceans, and rolling grasslands. Unique to the planet and its moon Concordia is beskar ore, a nearly indestructible material akin to iron.

      The warrior tradition of the Taung clans has been passed down through the ages and the unscrupulous denizens of the nearby Terminus Systems have learned to leave the planet well enough alone.

      Capital: Keldabe

      Orbital Period: 1.1 Earth Years
      Radius: 6440 km
      Day Length: 19 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.9 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 32 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.06 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Wilderness</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>65</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Jafar</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Jafar is a large, sulfurous gas giant with dark clouds of ash circling its atmosphere. Two reddish moons sit high in its orbit. The gravitational pull exerted by Jafar and its moons is slowly pulling Sultan, a nearby white dwarf star, out of position. Research suggests that the star’s collapse into a black hole could happen within the next quarter-million years.

      Orbital Period: 1.3 Earth Years
      Radius: 63,169 km
      Day Length: 1.3 Earth Years
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Sky</ImageGroup>
    <NotPlayable>true</NotPlayable>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>66</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Olkarion</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Olkarion is a terrestrial planet banded by a ring of mountains, casting the lower hemisphere into perpetual shadow. Protected from the heat of the sun, a vast forest of a tree species unique to the planet is able to flourish. The native Olkari were said to have almost magical abilities to shape the wood into various advanced forms. However, perhaps lured by these very rumors of super-technology, a turian expeditionary fleet was dispatched to the planet and the Olkari were wiped out shortly after. Unfortunately, whatever secrets they may have possessed died with them and the turians were unable to reproduce their success. The forest still stands, but is slowly dying off without the Olkari to tend it.

      Orbital Period: 1.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 7318 km
      Day Length: 28.4 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.6 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 32 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.4 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Wilderness</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>67</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Charlette II</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Charlette II is a gas giant containing trace amounts of oxygen. Research of the atmosphere indicates at one point there was significantly more oxygen, indicating a potential past cataclysmic event that removed the oxygen from the atmosphere. Theories suggest that a massive fire may have engulfed the planet and consumed the majority of its oxygen within a few days.

      Orbital Period: 47.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 32,191 km
      Day Length: 13.4 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Sky</ImageGroup>
    <NotPlayable>true</NotPlayable>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>68</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Telos IV</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      The planet Telos IV was once a world of natural beauty and home to a thriving ecosystem. Decades ago, civil war between two opposing political forces led to planetary bombardment, destroying significant parts of the ecosystem. A restoration project is underway to restore the planet to its former glory, with the planet sectioned off into chunks using mass effect fields.

      A space station orbits over the 45th northern latitude of the planet, which is used as a staging area and monitoring station for the restoration efforts. The majority of the population of Telos IV lives aboard this space station.

      Orbital Period: 6.7 Earth Years
      Radius: 4075 km
      Day Length: 24.9 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.6 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 5 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.3 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>SpaceStation</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>69</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Feros</PlanetName>
    <PlanetName2>Nirvash</PlanetName2>
    <PlanetDescription>
      %PLANETNAME% is a small, temperate planet notable for the vast reef-like growths forming the bulk of its landmass. The atmosphere is laced with trapar, a particulate matter linked to the biological activities of these growths. There are indications that %PLANETNAME% may have been mostly oceanic in the past and that the so-called ‘scub coral’ is a relatively new arrival, despite covering the vast majority of the planet’s surface. The ExoGeni Corporation founded a small colony to explore this unusual phenomena.

      %PLANETNAME% has two large moons, Eureka and Sakuya.

      Colony Founded: 2178
      Population: 300
      Capital: ExoGeni Building

      Orbital Period: 3.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 8366 km
      Day Length: 30.3 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 5.44 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 10 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.1 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Generic</ImageGroup>
    <ButtonLabel>Go sightseeing</ButtonLabel>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>70</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Sylux</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Sylux is a mostly barren planet that is difficult to scan or explore due to intense lightning storms covering the planet. The sole planetary outpost, Delano, is a popular hub for bounty hunters due to the difficulty involved in tracking ships near the surface.

      Orbital Period: 1.1 Earth Years
      Radius: 9547 km
      Day Length: 32.2 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 94.51 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 343 Celsius
      Surface Gravity 1.7 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Storm</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>71</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Ravka</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Ravka is a cold and intemperate planet that nonetheless has the ability to support life. Os Alta, the capital, is home to the bulk of the population. Known as Suli and led by the Lantsov royal family, the city is protected by an elite legion of biotically superior asari known as Grisha. For years they have held off the incursions of the Shu Han in the south and the Fjerdans in the north. The planet’s climate and remote location ensure very few external visitors, but in recent times, having a winter vacation home in Os Alta has become a status symbol among prominent asari.

      Orbital Period: 46.6 Earth Years
      Radius: 55,721 km
      Day Length: 14.6 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ButtonLabel>Book hotel</ButtonLabel>
    <ImageGroup>Ice</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>72</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Arche Koeln</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Arche Koeln is covered mostly by cold tundra and has no notable resources. The atmosphere is thick with metallic particles and various gases, giving the planet incredibly vibrant skies at sunrise and sunset. The remains of a Prothean temple are still relatively intact on the surface, surrounded by waterfalls and an ingenious aqueduct system. Though the temple has long been looted of anything historically significant, it is still a popular destination for photographers and anthropologists.

      Orbital Period: 9.0 Earth Years
      Radius: 7271 km
      Day Length: 13.8 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.91 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 7 Celsius
      Surface Gravity 3.2 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Ice</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>73</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Briona Gwydion</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Briona Gwydion is a small, rocky terrestrial planet. A massive range of mountains bisects the equator and stretches from pole to pole. Early survey teams dubbed it Dragonbein, after the famous sun dragon from salarian mythology, due to its bony, spine-like appearance. Its official name was later changed to the Keel Mountains to honor Captain Keel of the survey ship Sheraton, which was lost shortly after transmitting the results of its initial discovery.

      Orbital Period: 112.6 Earth Years
      Radius: 66,341 km
      Day Length: 18.6 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Generic</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>74</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Indieglut Lugh</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Indieglut Lugh is a pastoral planet with a dry atmosphere and nearly unspoiled surface. A network of cave rivers runs beneath the surface, home to a unique species of bioluminescent white trees that thrive in the slightly acidic water.

      The hanar established a small, experimental colony of drell on the planet a few years after the initial exodus from their home planet. The settlement thrived until a series of earthquakes rocked the planet, collapsing many of the underground tunnels and causing uncontrollable geysers to erupt from the surface. The resultant flooding wiped out most of the settlers and doomed the rest to a slow death by Kepral’s Syndrome.

      Orbital Distance: 12.6 AU
      Orbital Period: 34.4 Earth Years
      Radius: 8864 km
      Day Length: 35.6 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 2.1 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 32 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.2 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Generic</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>75</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Sif Berg</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      The proximity of Sif Berg’s star heats the planet to unbearable levels. Composed mostly of molten rock, the magma flow gives the surface an eerie, undulating appearance that can be seen from space with the naked eye. The rock is rich in several valuable materials, notably gold, but the challenge of extraction is a problem that has yet to be solved by any interested parties.

      Orbital Period: 0.4 Earth Years
      Radius: 7702 km
      Day Length: 67.0 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.18 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 523 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.3 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>LavaWorld</ImageGroup>
    <ButtonLabel>Fill water bottles</ButtonLabel>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>76</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Ran Hati</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Ran Hati is a small planet completely covered in boreal forest. Several biological expeditions have attempted to catalogue the numerous fauna that inhabit the surface, but most have ended in failure. The few that returned brought back only scant data implying the presence of monsters, but nothing viable for research. In scientific circles, Ran Hati is more commonly known as the “Forest of Pain”. Attempts to study the planet are now limited to high-atmosphere scans from an ExoGeni research ship stationed in perpetual orbit.

      Orbital Period: 9.5 Earth Years
      Radius: 3537 km
      Day Length: 64.9 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.37 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 18 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.39 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Wilderness</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>77</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Ramuh</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Ramuh is a hydrogen-helium gas giant. Charged ions in the sulfuric atmosphere have created billowing, cloudy storm fronts. Lightning can be seen flickering almost constantly across the dark side of the planet.

      The constellation Olduum, with its noticeably purple-hued stars, is visible even through the heavy cloud cover.

      Orbital Period: 113.1 Earth Years
      Radius: 52,290 km
      Day Length: 17.2 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Sky</ImageGroup>
    <NotPlayable>true</NotPlayable>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>78</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Ilos</PlanetName>
    <PlanetName2>Valyria</PlanetName2>
    <PlanetDescription>
      %PLANETNAME% was once a verdant world dotted with towering cities, home to a sect of Protheans known as the Freehold. However, all other history has been lost to the Doom of %PLANETNAME%. This massive eruption of volcanoes clouded the atmosphere with ash and turned the oceans to acid. The surface fractured into thousands of small, unstable islands. The cities collapsed into ruin and most of the written history of the planet was lost, along with their advances in science and technology.

      Some fragmentary records of the Doom survive in Prothean beacons, but study of the planet itself has yielded nothing of use.

      Orbital Period: 261 Earth Days
      Radius: 8607 km
      Day Length: 54.5 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 11.26 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 38 Celsius
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>DestroyedWorld</ImageGroup>
    <ButtonLabel>Go looting</ButtonLabel>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>79</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Megin Fi</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Megin Fi is a mid-sized gas giant with a pressure-cooker atmosphere composed mostly of chlorine. Its boiling cloud cover glows an eerie green from space.

      The wreckage of the aerostat colony Mag Mell still floats above its surface. The structure’s internal mass effect generators have long since failed and the city is now inverted. The upside-down towers and the ring cloud of rubble surrounding it are a popular setting for horror stories. They are also an excellent hiding place for small ships, and smugglers often make use of the area’s sensor distortion for illicit drops.

      Orbital Period: 0.4 Earth Years
      Radius: 6172 km
      Day Length: 53.5 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 84.30 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 510 Celsius
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Sky</ImageGroup>
    <NotPlayable>true</NotPlayable>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>80</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Coite-Bodher</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Coite-Bodher is a relatively small terrestrial planet with a desolate surface and recurrent earthquakes. Historical evidence indicates that massive fallout from a battle between the turians and batarians destroyed the once-lush planet. However, the cause of the battle has been systematically purged from all accessible records and is still unknown.

      Orbital Period: 33.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 30,488 km
      Day Length: 12.2 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Generic</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>81</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Newark</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Newark is a small, uninhabited planet that has warded off colonization due to the elliptical orbit of its star, which widens and narrows the habitable areas of the planet every year. Surface scans indicate a multiple small encampments that have been recently abandoned by small groups of various species that descended on the planet.

      Several crashed ships litter a canyon along the equator, recently flooded due to thawing of its glaciers.

      Orbital Period: 1.6 Earth Years
      Radius: 4910 km
      Day Length: 27.1 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.17 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 15 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.31 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Generic</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>82</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Predasis</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A world that could once be described as paradise, Predasis is a world currently held by the Ruhar krogan clan. It is currently under siege by the Kristang Coalition, a salarian group, after the capture of one of their diplomats. Becoming involved in this escalating conflict is not advised.

      Weakly encrypted signals from the krogan indicate there is a currently unknown species on the planet. This may be the real reason for the salarian presence in orbit.

      Orbital Period: 1.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 4,047 km
      Day Length: 26 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.05 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 27 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.83 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Farm</ImageGroup>
    <ButtonLabel>Investigate</ButtonLabel>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>83</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Decadia</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Decadia is a world devoid of intelligent life due to a nuclear war that took place 113 years ago. The last haven for the dominant species resided upon a scientific space colony that was in orbit at the time of global thermonuclear war.

      An investigation of the station revealed that the final members of the space colony’s population died due to oxygen recycler failure, less than two months before discovery by the salarians. All escape pods have been jettisoned from the station, signaling the possibility that a handful of the station’s residents attempted to escape their fate by returning to the irradiated planet.

      Orbital Period: 13.4 Earth Years
      Radius: 31,266 km
      Day Length: 21.5 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>SpaceStation</ImageGroup>
    <ButtonLabel>Investigate</ButtonLabel>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>84</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Mobius</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A world once rich with abundant life, Mobius is now a lifeless planet. Multiple world domination attempts culminated in a display of power that resulted in the destruction of one of the planet’s moons.

      Parts of the moon fell into the planet’s orbit and the impact destroyed the majority of the planet’s breathable atmosphere, ultimately killing off the ability to sustain life. The weapon used to destroy the planet remains abandoned in orbit, ironically named ‘Space Colony Ark’.

      Orbital Period: 6.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 9647 km
      Day Length: 44.7 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.22 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -108 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.2 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>DestroyedWorld</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>85</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Wald Uberlisterin</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A small, out-of-the-way terrestrial planet, Wald Uberlisterin is nonetheless notable for a castle-like rock formation on the northern pole. This ‘castle’ has become a topic of hot contention between anthropologist and geologists, with one side stating the formation is the remnant of an unknown civilization and the other side insisting it is merely the result of tectonic activity.

      Hoshichiri Heavy Industries, owners of the rights to surface mining on the planet, have elected to leave the formation untouched for now, undoubtedly hoping to extort large sums of money in exchange for maintaining its protected status.

      Orbital Period: 15.1 Earth Years
      Radius: 4645 km
      Day Length: 62.6 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.18 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -169 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.5 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Castle</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>86</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Cuchulainn</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Cuchulainn’s atmosphere consists of massive sulphur dioxide clouds, which flood the surface with acid rain. The Garamsythe Ocean, which covers most of the planet, rises an average of five millimeters per year. A brief Alliance survey suggests that the acidity of the water may eventually break down the terrestrial surface altogether.

      The planet glows a sickly green color when viewed from space, due to traces of ionized nitrogen in the upper atmosphere.

      Orbital Period: 5 Earth Years
      Radius: 5935 km
      Day Length: 53.2 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.91 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 94 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.94 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>WaterWorld</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>87</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Caerleon Medb</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Caerleon Medb is a small gas giant. While the planet itself contains large amounts of extractable helium-3, it is largely overlooked by mining companies in favor of its eight moons. Each moon contains vast quantities of separate materials, and the rights to mine them are continuously in contention. Sonax Industries currently holds the majority with five moons. Altai Mineral Works, notable for their success in eezo-refinery, have also established an orbital presence at Caerleon Medb.

      Orbital Period: 0.5 Earth Years
      Radius: 25,957 km
      Day Length: 18.1 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Sky</ImageGroup>
    <NotPlayable>true</NotPlayable>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>88</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Berk</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Berk is a small, mostly barren terrestrial world. A thin band of habitable terrain stretches along the coast of its massive ocean. A large island rises from the middle of the ocean and emits a plume of smoke that is visible from space.

      The planet is incapable of supporting plant life due to the sulfuric atmosphere and weak sun. Each of the several varieties of native fauna are well-adapted, however. Possessing scales, wings, and claws, they are able to live and hunt in the rocky outcroppings near the sea.

      Orbital Period: 1.7 Earth Years
      Radius: 2843 km
      Day Length: 34.0 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.00 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 18 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.28 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Ocean</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>89</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Narshe</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Narshe is a snow-covered planet with a surface composed mostly of coal. Human mining teams stripped much of the resource away, but as time went on and eezo became more common, the planet was largely abandoned.

      Recently, however, a vein of frozen magicite was discovered beneath the surface. The unknown conglomerate with controlling shares in the Esper Mine has declined to comment on their plans for this unexpected find.

      Orbital Period: 35.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 3718 km
      Day Length: 39.5 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.15 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -96 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.39 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Ice</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>90</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Midgar</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Midgar is a heavily industrialized planet. Home to a powerful energy source simply known as ‘mako’, the surface is covered by Shinra Company’s massive harvesting installations. The Cetra, original inhabitants of the planet who opposed the aggressive draining of its resources, have been largely forced offworld or into hiding.

      With the dominance of eezo, however, mako has been mostly relegated to smaller applications. New research also suggests that long-term exposure may be irreversibly toxic to most species.

      Orbital Period: 123.6 Earth Years
      Radius: 7304 km
      Day Length: 57.7 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.42 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -118 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.99 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Factory</ImageGroup>
    <ButtonLabel>Bring gas mask</ButtonLabel>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>91</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Natina</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Natina is a barren, volcanic terrestrial world with an atmosphere choked in soot. The planet’s incredibly strong gravity and atmospheric pressure causes the magma eruptions to condense and harden almost immediately. The resulting surface is deep black and ash-laden winds have scoured it to almost uniformly reflective sheen.

      This unique display, along with the frequent volcanic eruptions, makes Natina a popular destination for artists of all kinds. The planet has been affectionately dubbed ‘Yellow’ by many photography fans, alluding to the distinctive cover of the famous Galactic Geographic holozine.

      Orbital Period: 0.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 6865 km
      Day Length: 56.2 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 5.73 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 37 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 2.78 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>LavaWorld</ImageGroup>
    <ButtonLabel>Deploy Bob Ross VI</ButtonLabel>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>92</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Spira</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Spira is an oceanic world and the bulk of its landmass consists of islands. The remains of seaports along several of the coastlines seem to suggest the planet was inhabited at one time. Sub-surface scanning indicates the presence of several underwater structures.

      Massive tidal waves make any surface landing attempts extremely difficult. A high plateau, dubbed Zanarkand after the first ship to successfully touch down on the planet, offers the only relatively safe staging area for exploration.

      Orbital Period: 2.3 Earth Years
      Radius: 7074 km
      Day Length: 47.6 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.33 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 35 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.1 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Ocean</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>93</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Cleyra</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Cleyra is a large gas giant. Winds generated by the planet’s rapid rotation whip the particulate-choked atmosphere into a perpetual sandstorm. Completely obscured to most sensors, a tight-beam scan of the surface was nonetheless able to detect a crystalline structure near the core.

      Observation ships stationed in high orbit have recorded fragments of chant-like audio emanating from Cleyra’s surface. Linguists studying the recordings were unable to match the sounds to any currently known language.

      Orbital Period: 5.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 3718 km
      Day Length: 1.3 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.06 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -124 Celsius
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Sky</ImageGroup>
    <NotPlayable>true</NotPlayable>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>94</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Efrafa</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Efrafa is a high-gravity terrestrial planet. Its rolling fields are criss-crossed by large tunnels and trenches. The origin of these warrens is unknown, but they provide a convenient home for several small elcor communities. These are collectively governed by a council of elcor elders known as the Owsla.

      A raiding attack led by a vorcha mercenary known as Woundwort nearly succeeded in wiping out the colony. However, the elcor retreated into the warrens and collapsed the tunnels behind them, burying the vorcha in the rubble. The elcor ballad “Dhinsaa Erazi Ershan”, or “The Heroism of Hazel” honors the leader of the Owsla, whose actions were instrumental in saving the colony.

      Orbital Period: 115.6 Earth Years
      Radius: 4911 km
      Day Length: 30.3 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.63 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 12 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 10.28 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Generic</ImageGroup>
    <NotPlayable>true</NotPlayable>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>95</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>96</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>97</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Zonama Sekot</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A tropical hothouse of a planet, Zonama Sekot is a lush paradise. The myths of the long extinct Ferroans, preserved only in rudimentary holo-form, state that Zonama is possessed of basic sentience, the spirit of which is called Sekot. Star charts recovered from ruins indicate the planet may have moved through several different solar systems in its lifetime. The surface does bear massive scorch marks near the equator, giving some credence to the idea of a planet capable of space travel, but no current research can suggest how this feat might be accomplished.

      Surface travel is discouraged due to a virulent strain of spore-borne bacteria in the air.

      Orbital Period: 1.0 Earth Years
      Radius: 5693 km
      Day Length: 20.6 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.16 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 25 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.9G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Wilderness</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>98</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Isabela</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Isabela is a large planet tidally locked to a small dwarf star. As a result, temperatures are frigid and much of the surface lies in perpetual dark. Massive oceans composed of liquified methane cover more than 90 percent of the planet’s mass.

      Isabela is a haunt for pirates. Its extreme conditions and ever-shifting surface make it easy to lose any pursuers. Many of the planet’s more frequent visitors have modified their spacecraft for oceanic landings, and the methane seas provide a cheap source of energy for those equipped to harvest it.

      Orbital Period: 21.0 Earth Years
      Radius: 9749 km
      Day Length: 45.4 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.4 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -171 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.5 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>WaterWorld</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>99</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Nibel</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Nibel is a small planet mostly covered in withered forest. Survey scans from low atmosphere detected a transmission from an unknown location. When decoded and viewed, the rudimentary images seem to depict a cataclysmic explosion of light. Satellite imaging of the surface reveals a ring-like pattern of destruction. Current scientific theories posit that gravitational pulses from Sein, the system’s star, may have triggered a violent release of stored energy in the planet’s core.

      The planet’s three moons - Ginso, Gumon, and Horu - are similarly barren, though the source of their destruction is not clearly observed.

      Orbital Distance: 11.3 AU
      Orbital Period: 69.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 1183 km
      Day Length: 30.4 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 22.4 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -130 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.6 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Generic</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>100</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Themyscira</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Themyscira is a temperate world. Its surface is dotted with large islands. Considered a backwater by most, the planet is a haven for a small colony of raloi. This splinter tribe of warriors, known as the Bana-Mighdall, withdrew to Themyscira in order to preserve their culture away from the influence of the Citadel races. They eschew most modern technology and their society is heavily rooted in polytheistic principles. Though many have become hunters and craftsmen, the majority of the Bana-Mighdall still retain their warrior traditions of old.

      Orbital Period: 111.7 Earth Years
      Radius: 40,394 km
      Day Length: 19.1 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Generic</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>101</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>102</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <IsAsteroid>true</IsAsteroid>
    <PlanetName>Metallic Asteroid</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A metal-rich asteroid.
      Radius: 91 km
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>103</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Prometheus</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A spiked ball floating in space, Prometheus is a world covered in grandiose spikes that make reaching the surface a one-way trip for any flying aircraft. As the only catalogued planet with this type of geography, it has proven difficult for science teams to determine what could have caused such a uniform distribution of mass.

      Acidic rain pummels the surface for half of Prometheus’ solar year, wearing away spikes over time. New spikes appear to crop up every few hundred years without any obvious signs of tectonic activity beneath the surface of the planet.

      The orbit of the planet around the star is an odd elliptical path, leading some to question whether something knocked Prometheus out of a circular orbit.

      Orbital Period: 1.1 Earth Years
      Radius: 6,210 km
      Day Length: 32.4 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.21 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 22 Celsius
      Surface Gravity 1.3 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Spikes</ImageGroup>
    <NotPlayable>true</NotPlayable>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>104</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Echo II</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A simple planet with a crust mostly made of obsidian, Echo II is a lifeless planet with an almost glass-like surface. Near the north pole are the remains of what appears to be a long-range monitoring station, built by an unknown species. This base is the only indication that sentient life ever existed on Echo II.

      An investigation into the purpose of the monitoring station yielded few meaningful results; the only salvageable piece of information from the dated technology shows that the station was monitoring a planet in the system - a planet that appears to no longer exist.

      Orbital Period: 0.4 Earth Years
      Radius: 6894 km
      Day Length: 58.6 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.40 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 120 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.3 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Desert</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>105</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Mononoke</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Traces of sodium in the atmosphere give Mononoke its overall dark grey color, but it is otherwise a typical hydrogen-helium gas giant. An abundance of water vapor in the upper atmosphere accounts for its white clouds.

      A long-range probe recorded footage of a brief phenomena in which the surface of the planet appeared to be covered in long, trailing spores.

      Orbital Period: 57.6 Earth Years
      Radius: 59,729 km
      Day Length: 14.0 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Sky</ImageGroup>
    <NotPlayable>true</NotPlayable>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>106</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Nullam</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      One of the larger mysteries in the galaxy, Nullam is an uninhabited planet that has been largely unexplored by the spacefaring species of the Milky Way. The surface appears to be mostly made of lava in the southern hemisphere, with a breathable atmosphere in the northern hemisphere that could sustain life - if one was foolish enough to attempt to land.

      Intense, physics-defying gravity waves emanate from Nullam, causing certain locations on the planet to have a gravitational shearing effect. When these mysterious gravity waves collide, anything with significant mass at the point of collision is torn apart in multiple directions.

      Orbital Period: 141.9 Earth Years
      Radius: 22,479 km
      Day Length: 10.9 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Generic</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>107</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Valum</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Distant Valum has seen only a cursory examination by an unmanned probe, with a more in-depth survey scheduled for 2190. It has a trace atmosphere of nitrogen and argon. The initial scan shows a few uninhabited facilities in a formation similar to common manufacturing assembly yards. With the planet long abandoned, the facilities have degraded into a frozen ghost town.

      Unusual artificial gravity waves have been detected originating from beneath the surface of several of the facilities, leading to the hypothesis that Valum was producing gravity-altering devices before being unsafely shut down. The generated waves are detectable from tens of millions of kilometers away, likely indicating that the produced devices were weapons-grade or meant to move planet-sized objects.

      Orbital Period: 275.4 Earth Years
      Radius: 7623 km
      Day Length: 47.4 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.14 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -176 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.9 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Ice</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>108</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>Placeholder</PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>109</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Vetus Domum</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Vetus Domum has a smooth, curvy landscape covered in ash from at least tens of thousands of years ago. Strong planetary winds carry this ash, whittling down any structures that stand out on the surface.

      The initial unmanned probe sent to the surface showed remains of buildings under the ash, safe from the harsh wind. Further investigation indicated that Vetus Domum was once a very populated planet, possibly the capital homeworld of a species that lived tens of thousands of years ago.

      No remains of bodies were detected by the probes, indicating that Vetum Domum’s inhabitants may have completely abandoned the planet. A faint radio signal emanating from beneath the surface constantly broadcasts the word ‘Prometheus’.

      Orbital Period: 2.7 Earth Years
      Radius: 5729 km
      Day Length: 50.3 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.8 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -40 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.87 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Generic</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>110</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Niihama</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Niihama is a heavily industrialized world run entirely by corporations. Genex Chemical, a bioengineering firm, has faced several large-scale uprisings in recent years. With automation rapidly reducing the need for cheap labor, most of the planet’s workforce is unemployed and unable to leave the surface. An extremist faction known as Individual Eleven has claimed responsibility for at least three of the outbreaks.

      Sector 9, a combined-race special ops task force, is working with the planet’s corporate leaders to resolve the situation.

      TRAVEL WARNING: Due to violent social unrest and acts of terrorism, all incoming and outgoing traffic to Niihama is restricted.

      Orbital Period: 1.0 Earth Years
      Radius: 1528 km
      Day Length: 1.0 Earth Years
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.00 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 55 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.1 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Factory</ImageGroup>
    <NotPlayable>true</NotPlayable>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>111</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Valholl</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Valholl is an icy planet perhaps most notable for its status as a sacred burial ground. At the height of their uplifting, krogan warriors who fell in honorable battle were retrieved from the battlefields. Their bodies were prepared and transported to the frozen surface of Valholl to be interred. The genophage has all but wiped out the ancient traditions of feasting and celebrating the lives of the fallen, and the planet is seldom visited. Only the crooked shafts of ceremonial spears plunged into the ground mark the passage of thousands.

      Orbital Period: 18.1 Earth Years
      Radius: 11190 km
      Day Length: 47.2 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.20 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -136 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.7 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Ice</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>112</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Zeromus</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Zeromus is a large hydrogen-helium gas giant. Its massive gravity well has attracted hundreds of moons and asteroids into its orbit. Most are ripped apart by the forces and become part of an ever-growing ring system. Indigo vapor trails make a faint haze in the atmosphere as the planet’s solid copper core slowly collapses under the pressure.

      The planet is commonly called "the Condemner", and not even pirates venture too close. Even out of the gravity well’s range, the sheer amount of space debris can obliterate all but the most strongly-shielded ships.

      Orbital Period: 39.1 Earth Years
      Radius: 72,492 km
      Day Length: 17.7 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Sky</ImageGroup>
    <NotPlayable>true</NotPlayable>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
























  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>113</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Caelondia</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Caelondia is a fractured collection of land masses held together by the gravitational force of its planetary core. The remains of a surface installation can be seen on the largest of the pieces. Known as the Bastion, the facility was created by the Mancers as a weapon to destroy their sworn enemies, the Ura. Attempts to use the weapon resulted in a catastrophic backfire that blew the planet apart. This event later became known as the Calamity.

      Though the planet itself is uninhabitable, a small number of Ura and Mancers survived the Calamity. Relegated to small outposts on Zia and Zulf, the system’s two moons, these rival factions engage in a never-ending series of skirmishes with each other.

      Orbital Period: 73.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 4926 km
      Day Length: 23.3 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.00 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -193 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.7 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>DestroyedWorld</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>114</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>115</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <IsAsteroid>true</IsAsteroid>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Cluster</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A collection of small siliceous asteroids, loosely bound together by gravity.
      Radius: 12 km
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>116</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>117</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Therum</PlanetName>
    <PlanetName2>Tellus</PlanetName2>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Decades ago, %PLANETNAME% was once a human colony. In the years prior to the loss of the colony, an unknown species invaded the planet. A staunch resistance by the Alliance staved off the alien invaders for a number of years, but in the following years several of the planetary leaders opened a dialogue with the aliens, attempting to bring an end to the conflict.

      To the population of %PLANETNAME%, it became clear that the aliens were trying to help them ascend to the heavens, and that their original invasion attempts were due to miscommunications between species. The aliens gave a gift of their own technology to the humans, allowing them to enhance their bodies in ways that pleased the masses, such as improvements to human vision and legs that don’t become tired.

      Years after the last human embraced the improvements, the aliens declared that all humans must leave %PLANETNAME% for their salvation. Due to the decades of propaganda that the humans all fell for, nearly all left without a second thought, and the ones that stayed behind have never been heard from again.

      The aliens appear to have decided to strip mine the planet, the surface now covered in craters and mining facilities.

      Orbital Period: 6.4 Earth Years
      Radius: 6724 km
      Day Length: 28.3 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.68 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 39 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.12 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>LavaWorld</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>118</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Cloudbank</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Cloudbank is a small world almost completely covered by mechanical terraforming. Records salvaged from Goldwalk, the capital city, indicate that this vast disruption of the landscape is due to a rogue robotic force. This force, called the Process, was an ever-evolving system once utilized by the municipal administrators to change the landscape and environment of the city. In their zeal for ever more perfected technology, the architects eventually lost control when the Process began to develop outside its original limitations and it swiftly consumed the planet.

      Alliance probes of the system show a higher than normal concentration of geth signals. Whether they are somehow tied to the planet’s fate or merely curious bystanders has yet to be determined.

      Orbital Period: 0.3 Earth Years
      Radius: 4238 km
      Day Length: 57.2 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.27 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 51 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.63 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Factory</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>119</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Oculon</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Oculon is a terrestrial world with a nitrogen-oxygen atmosphere containing trace amounts of hydrocarbons. While the planet appears to be ripe for habitation, no species has ever followed through with colonization of the surface due to the low value of the other planets in the system. Several space stations orbit the planet; originally used as staging areas for the original planetary expeditions, most are now abandoned.

      Several space stations of salarian design appear to have significant damage; however, due to looting, the cause has been lost to time.

      Orbital Period: 33.9 Earth Years
      Radius: 4572 km
      Day Length: 45.6 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.9 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 6 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.09 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>SpaceStation</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>120</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Vermillion</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Vermillion is a terrestrial world with several regions that could be considered part of a paradise planet. Other parts of the planet are uninhabitable due to limited ozone protecting them from the system’s star. The more densely-covered areas are common vacation destinations for a variety of species.

      Space travel onto the planet is limited to its capital spaceport, Phenac City, in an effort to improve the planet’s appeal as a relaxation destination. Transport to various parts of the planet is done by more rudimentary means, such as cruise ships to renowned locations such as Vermillion City, Olivine, and the Sevii Islands.

      Orbital Period: 5.3  Earth Years
      Radius: 6077 km
      Day Length: 21 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.1 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 27 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.8 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Ocean</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>121</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Medoh</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A small oxygen-nitrogen gas giant, Medoh has been developed as a full-featured testing ground for aerodynamic non-spacefaring vehicle design. Constant winds that swirl due to the high rotation rate of the planet provide excellent conditions for testing unpredictable wind patterns on habitable planets. Due to the relatively small size of the planet, combined with the high rate of rotation, it is expected to lose most of its atmosphere within the next 10,000 years.

      The single moon of Medoh, Revali, is uncharted except for a single tower that marks an otherwise unremarkable surface.

      Orbital Period: 470.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 1,350 km
      Day Length: 2.5 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Sky</ImageGroup>
    <NotPlayable>true</NotPlayable>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>122</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>123</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroid>true</IsAsteroid>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Distress signal</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A distress call is coming from this asteroid; however, nothing adorns the surface except for a single large tunnel entrance. The distress call signal is weak and appears to be coming from the asteroid’s interior, repeating a message about ‘giant alien spiders’.

      This is almost certainly a trap. While giant alien spiders are no joke, risking the Normandy to save these unknown victims is certainly not worth the risk.

      Radius: 127 km
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>124</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>125</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <IsAsteroid>true</IsAsteroid>
    <PlanetName>Carbonaceous Asteroid</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A dark, carbon-rich asteroid.
      Radius: 83 km
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>126</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Liara's Dig Site</PlanetName>
    <ImageGroup>Error</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>127</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Vah Rudania</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Vah Rudania is a hot, barren terrestrial world. Chiseled into the surface are maze-like patterns, with scans indicating a subterranean tunnel system that can be entered from specific points in the maze. The surface is dotted with these labyrinths, though no surface-dwelling life appears to be able to survive the intense heat to make use of them.

      The single moon of Vah Rudania, Daruk, has several large craters on its surface. The few colonial areas on the moon have a planetary defense system to defend against incoming meteors.

      Radius: 5171 km
      Day Length: 60.5 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.84 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 180 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.87
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>LavaWorld</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>128</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Ruta</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Ruta is a water planet with a very cold terrestrial atmosphere. Volcanic activity under the planetary ocean and water currents keep the majority of the surface from freezing. A haven for marine life, Ruta has many unexplored secrets in its depths.

      A colonized moon of Ruta, Mipha, is considered one of the leading pioneers in medical science. The moon’s capital research facility, named Mipha’s Grace, contributed significantly to the development of medi-gel in partnership with the Sirta Foundation.

      Orbital Period: 0.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 10,480 km
      Day Length: 56.7 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.96 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -60 Celsius
      Surface gravity: 0.98 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>WaterWorld</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>129</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Orokin</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Orokin is a relatively small terrestrial planet. Its inhabitants, ruled by an elite few, became obsessed with researching and exploiting an unknown resource known as the Void. An experiment gone wrong resulted in a generation of Orokin gifted with unnatural and often fatal powers. The research of an Archimedian geneticist was able to devise a method of transferring these Orokin into new bodies, or frames. Records after this point become few and far between due to a massive uprising simply known as The Old War.

      Modern scientists are still uncertain about the exact identity of the Void, but many have pointed out its apparent resemblance to modern biotics. Historians also make note of the Sentient, a race of synthetic beings created by the Orokin and who existed centuries prior to the quarians’ creation of the geth.

      Orbital Period: 0.7 Earth Years
      Radius: 38,482 km
      Day Length: 16.2 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Generic</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>130</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Vigrid</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Vigrid is a large planet with an errant orbit. Umbra, a nearby black hole, vies with Lumen, the system’s star, for gravitational control of the planet. A small red moon was pulled into the system several decades ago; its orbit is slowly decaying and drawing it nearer to Umbra.

      Two separate probes sent by expeditionary forces noted a strange anomaly. The first probe recorded Vigrid’s position much nearer to Lumen, with a lush and almost golden surface. The second probe, sent several years after the first, noted a shift toward Umbra and a barren surface covered in molten magma. A third probe, Jubileus, has been dispatched by the salarians to record any new developments in the system.

      Orbital Period: 1.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 4327 km
      Day Length: 63.9 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.52 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 136 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.46 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Generic</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>131</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Anathema</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Anathema is a small, dark planet in a backwater system. The planet itself is of minimal importance. However, astronomers have been able to predict several events in other parts of the galaxy based on careful observation of the unusual star and wind patterns in Anathema’s vicinity.

      These observations, collected over a span of approximately 350 years, have accurately forecasted everything from ship crashes to supernova stars. A later-published compilation, titled The Nice and Accurate Prophecies, is a popular read among aspiring astronomers and many universities offer trips to Anathema as part of their curriculum.

      Orbital Period: 4.0 Earth Years
      Radius: 9508 km
      Day Length: 32.1 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.40 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -78 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.90
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Generic</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>132</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Druidia</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Planet Druidia is the kingdom of King Roland, led by his daughter and heir Princess Vespa. Due to the low natural gravity, the planet is outfitted with a full containment shield to keep the atmosphere intact, and only allows entry or exit from the planet at the plantary airlock. Because of this shield and other environmental modifications (such as a gravity naturalizer that increases gravity for things over a certain mass), it is known to have a large supply of fresh air.

      President Skroob and Dark Helmet of rival Planet Spaceball recently attempted to suck the air out of Planet Druidia through the containment shield’s airlock and use it to save their own planet. Their attempts were stymied by a mercenaries Lone Starr and Mog when the capital ship ‘Mega Maid’ was destroyed.

      The Druidians have since built a stronger planetary defenses into the containment shield to better protect themselves.

      Orbital Period: 1.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 5501 km
      Day Length: 31.1 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.89 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 22 Celsius
      Natural Gravity: 0.45 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Generic</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>133</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Spaceball</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Despite their planet being on the verge of a catastrophic collapse, the people of Planet Spaceball seem oblivious to other inhabitable planets in the Milky Way. Due to a lack of proper carbon recycling flora across the surface, the supply of fresh air on the planet has reached critically low levels and will soon be unable to sustain the majority of the population.

      The leader of Planet Spaceball, President Skroob, has been missing for several months following a failed mission to suck the atmosphere out of Planet Druidia. In this last-ditch effort to save the planet, the capital ship Spaceball I was destroyed, leading to a vacuum of power in Planet Spaceball’s line of succession.

      Orbital Period: 15.3 Earth Years
      Radius: 1831 km
      Day Length: 16 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.61 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 10 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.78 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>City</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>134</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Stardew</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Stardew is a pastoral planet with a small population of salarians, whose technological savvy has been put to good use improving the agricultural industry. Though the farms are limited in scale and most of Stardew’s inhabitants live in modestly-sized communes, the planet is nonetheless able to sustain a small export of quality foodstuffs.

      Joja Corporation has expressed interest in commercializing Stardew’s operations. However, the Citadel economic protection clauses granted to planets dependent on subsistence agriculture have so far made it almost impossible for the corporation to interfere.

      Orbital Period: 2.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 11,496 km
      Day Length: 18.6 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Farm</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>135</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Godric</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      An otherwise unremarkable planet, Godric does have one noticeable feature - a massive crater near the equator. Scientists speculate that a small astral body may have crashed to the surface at some point in the past. The crater, Godric’s Hollow, holds an acid lake for much of the year. Snake-like cracks spread from its edge in all directions.

      A popular extranet webcomic uses Godric as a setting for its villain, a mad salarian mage who split his soul to create objects of immortality and then deposited them at the bottom of the lake.

      Orbital Period: 25.3 Earth Years
      Radius: 5130 km
      Day Length: 5.2 Earth Years
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.49 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 22 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.47 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Generic</ImageGroup>
    <ButtonLabel>Get SCUBA gear</ButtonLabel>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>136</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Belmont</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Belmont is a world from another age. Left alone for the majority of the ascendance of the Citadel races, it is technologically backward, but rich in art and architecture. A large castle stands on the surface, preserved from the ravages of time by unknown means. Alliance teams sent to study the structure reported an appearance very similar to the gothic architecture of Old Earth.

      The recent discovery of the Long Library, though the text in the books is written in an indecipherable language, nonetheless provided valuable information. Most notably, Belmont’s inhabitants bore a striking resemblance to the human vampire. Unfortunately, no trace of them remains, leading many to surmise that they may have simply left their small empire and gone elsewhere.

      Orbital Period: 399.7 Earth Years
      Radius: 69,862 km
      Day Length: 14.4 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Castle</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>137</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Vie de Marli</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Vie de Marli is a planet with several large continents. The largest of these, Dumary, is home to Uroboros City. Founded by multimillionaire volus businessman Arius, the city boasts an impressive array of mining conglomerates who strip the nearby mountains of valuable ore. Skyscraper Sanctum, the headquarters of Uroboros Corporation, towers over the center of the city.

      Most notably, Vie de Marli is also the birthplace of the Argosax Cult, a small tribe that worships a malevolent, multidimensional god. The Cult claims that Uroboros is secretly mining for Arcanas, not ore. The corporation has declined to comment on this accusation.

      Orbital Period: 1.7 Earth Years
      Radius: 1170 km
      Day Length: 24.8 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.78 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 13 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.48 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>City</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>138</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>Placeholder</PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>139</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <IsAsteroid>true</IsAsteroid>
    <PlanetName>Carbonaceous Asteroid</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A dark asteroid of mixed carbonaceous materials.
      Radius: 42 km
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>140</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Sochen</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Sochen is a barren planet with an extensive underground cave network. Sonic scans from low atmosphere reveal an almost palace-like appearance to the structures beneath the surface. The initial probe sent to roam the tunnels was destroyed by a blast of biotic energy in its most rudimentary form. However, it was able to transmit a few static images before going dark, which show intricate carvings on some of the cave walls. The last transmitted image (code-named Mandragora) appears to be a creature of some kind, though it more closely resembles a turnip.

      Orbital Distance: 10,367,883 km
      Orbital Period: 0.6 Earth Years
      Radius: 4534 km
      Day Length: 0.6 Earth Years
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.02 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 151 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.8 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Cave</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>141</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Golmore</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Golmore is a planet thickly covered with jungle. A thin blue shimmer can be seen in the upper atmosphere. Ships attempting to pass this unusual barrier are repelled by forces unseen.

      A turian task force stationed in the system noted a single ship descending into the atmosphere in 2113. A ping of its transponder returned a Viera-class freighter running under the name Jagd Difohr, a description matching nothing in any known navy at the time. The ship has not reappeared since.

      Orbital Period: 812.3 Earth Years
      Radius: 6788 km
      Day Length: 41.2 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 2.35 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 37 Celsius
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Sky</ImageGroup>
    <NotPlayable>true</NotPlayable>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>142</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Ragnarok</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Ragnarok is a dry, lifeless planet discovered by the Asari in 2076. The planet is covered in a star-bleached tint, indicating that a period of intense solar radiation occurred on the planet. Investigations on the planet’s surface found ample evidence suggesting intelligent life was extinguished on Ragnarok around 2021. Further investigation found several inscriptions by inhabitants, detailing the dominant species’ final days.

      An intense solar flare impacted the planet, disrupting communications and effectively poisoning anyone not directly shielded from the radiation. This solar flare killed off the majority of the planet’s life in a matter of days. The remaining population, congregated in small camps around the planet, planned for the continuation of the species with their remaining resources.

      Several of these solar shelters show obvious signs of sabotage, indicating that some members of these encampments became deranged and actively destroyed the protective shielding. Study of the local star shows that the solar flare should have ended sometime around 2023, leading to the conclusion that the rest of the population likely starved to death.

      Orbital Period: 1.5 Earth Years
      Radius: 5729 km
      Day Length: 31 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.7 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 32 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.05 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>DestroyedWorld</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>143</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Darnassus</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Darnassus is a mid-sized terrestrial planet. Swathes of its surface have been burned by fire, but in recent years the plant life has begun to return. Most notable is Teldrassil, the World Tree. An eccentric hanar sect known as the Fandral Druids planted this tree near the planet’s apex as part of a ritual to restore vitality to Darnassus. Under their careful tending, the tree has reached astronomical heights and its crown is visible in the upper atmosphere.

      Orbital Period: 0.5 Earth Years
      Radius: 73,314 km
      Day Length: 26.9 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Generic</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>144</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>145</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <IsAsteroid>true</IsAsteroid>
    <PlanetName>Rocky Asteroid</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      An asteroid composed of mixed metals and silicates.
      Radius: 54 km
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>146</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>147</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Falkreath</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Falkreath is a moderately-sized, chilly planet in a backwater system. A large valley cuts through the southwestern hemisphere. Free from the snow and ice that grips the rest of Falkreath’s surface, this valley is home to one of the galaxy’s largest known graveyards. Originally said to be the final resting place of famed turian Siddgeir, it soon became the resting place of many others who requested to be interred near the honored commander.

      The valley, known as Helgen, was blockaded in 2172 by the Hierarchy to maintain what little sanctity remained of the site. This has not stopped smugglers from making runs for the sole purpose of dumping bodies, only half of whom have actually requested a Helgen burial.

      Orbital Period: 5.9 Earth Years
      Radius: 5727 km
      Day Length: 55.3 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.42 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -121 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.85 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Ice</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>148</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Seath</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Seath is a gas giant with unique crystal formations floating up from its surface. Pressurized minerals are formed in the core and explosively dislodged once they become too large. These crystals reflect much of the star’s light, giving the planet an eerie pale glow and making visual navigation nearly impossible.

      An Alliance tow ship was able to cast a line to one of these crystals and remove it from the atmosphere for further study. Though most of it was sent to a research lab, a small specimen of this Primordial Crystal was gifted to the Citadel and can be viewed in the Mineral Archives.

      Orbital Period: 46.7 Earth Years
      Radius: 60,948 km
      Day Length: 67.1 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Sky</ImageGroup>
    <NotPlayable>true</NotPlayable>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>149</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Estus</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Estus is an enormous gas giant that on first glance could be mistaken for a star. Gases in the atmosphere constantly ignite under the heat of the planet’s sun, wreathing the surface in orange flames. Despite the maelstrom, the planet’s geomagnetic field is incredibly strong and can safely discharge even a capital ship’s drive core in very little time, making it a common destination during fleet maneuvers.

      A salarian engineering team recently discovered that Estus’ unique composition of ignited atmospheric gases can be pressurized into a liquid form, after which it can be used to create incredibly strong welds on ship hulls.

      Orbital Period: 17.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 10,510 km
      Day Length: 49.8 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Sky</ImageGroup>
    <NotPlayable>true</NotPlayable>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>150</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Glaurung</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Glaurung is a gas giant with a large core composed mostly of molten gold. The lack of surface fission makes it an attractive candidate for space-to-surface mining. However, an atmosphere composed largely of toxic gases caused the workers in these stations to sink into delirium. Many began to hallucinate and the ensuing chaos rendered most of the drills inoperable, either due to mechanical destruction or simply because all the workers were dead.

      The skeletal remains of the stations can still be seen floating in low orbit.

      Orbital Period: 1.1 Earth Years
      Radius: 7819 km
      Day Length: 44.6 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Sky</ImageGroup>
    <NotPlayable>true</NotPlayable>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>151</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Thayserix</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Thayserix is a nitrogen-based gas giant with a heavy cover of swirling cumulonimbus clouds. Massive rock spires jut into the upper atmosphere and act as electrical conductors during the planet’s frequent lightning storms. Its magnetic field is unusual, consisting of two misaligned poles and a third ‘pseudo-pole’ that heavily distort most navigational instruments. Increases in shield power and computing speed have made a closer approach possible in recent years, though most captains still prefer to avoid the system entirely.

      According to legend, an Altean ship was able to make a surface run of the planet using a freeze ray, but the extinction of their species has made any hope of recreating this feat with current technology nearly impossible.

      Orbital Period: 0.5 Earth Years
      Radius: 9616 km
      Day Length: 47.0 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Sky</ImageGroup>
    <NotPlayable>true</NotPlayable>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>152</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Lagavulin</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Lagavulin is a mid-sized planet most notable for two things: its precisely calculable data, and the stone spire that soars hundreds of kilometers from the surface. The spire’s origins and purpose are unknown, and despite several years of study, the method of its construction is also still unknown.

      A small, almost cult-like ritual known as ‘slaying’ has sprung up around the spire, whereupon adventurers attempt to reach the top from the inside. The vast majority of the planet’s life forms also reside within the spire, making it an incredibly dangerous prospect that grants immense prestige to those few who achieve the summit.

      Orbital Period: 3.0 Earth Years
      Radius: 5000 km
      Day Length: 55.0 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 3.0 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 20 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.0 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Spire</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>153</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Erathia</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Erathia is a planet ravaged by war. Set at strategic FTL crossroads, it has been under the control of several different factions in as many years. Originally the domain of the turian ruler Gryphonheart, it was sacked in 2036 by the warlord Eeofel and his krogan army, and again in 2042 by a batarian force under the leadership of Nighon. In 2047, the Council dispatched the Bracada, an asari peacekeeping brigade, to Erathia. Further bolstered by salarian STG cell AvLee, the Bracada returned the planet to a semblance of order. After several uprisings threatened to topple the tentative peace, the Council dispatched the Deyja fleet to crush the last hopes of any would-be usurpers.

      Orbital Period: 84.4 Earth Years
      Radius: 65,976 km
      Day Length: 14.0 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>DestroyedWorld</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>154</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Cayde-6</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Cayde-6 is a tiny dwarf planet with a trace atmosphere. The surface is mainly composed of water ice trapped beneath a skin of weak ammonia ice. Bioluminescent plankton beneath the surface spread a faint bluish glow through the frozen layers.

      Orbital Period: 238.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 1402 km
      Day Length: 30.2 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.04 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -211 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.1 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Ice</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>155</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Tenenbaum</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Tenenbaum is an oceanic world with no landmass. It is barren on the surface, but an unusual ecosystem flourishes beneath the waves. Despite the planet’s use as a former dumping ground for scientific waste, spent ordnance, and other toxic substances, Tenenbaum’s native life forms have adapted and prospered. Environmental scientists have successfully lobbied the Council to place the planet under protective status.

      Tenenbaum still attracts its fair share of pirates and lowlifes, but most are driven off by a privately developed force of automatons facetiously referred to as ‘Big Daddies’.

      Orbital Period: 3.6 Earth Years
      Radius: 5988 km
      Day Length: 22.2 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 2.63 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 23 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.9 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>WaterWorld</ImageGroup>
    <NotPlayable>true</NotPlayable>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>156</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Terraria</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      The planet Terraria is a ball of garbage floating through space. Originally just a dump of someone’s trash, a large enough accumulation of mass in a single location caused the space waste to form its own gravity well. Tens of thousands of years of space waste from tourism has led to Terraria becoming a recognized celestial body by the Citadel Council.

      There are giant holes dug to the core of the ‘planet’, as well as installations that have no discernable value. In 1744, the Citadel Council decided that Terraria would be henceforth known as ‘the trash planet’. Today, caravans of various species take vacations to dump their trash and make their own mark upon the galaxy.

      The economy of Terraria is booming due to the fees the planet owners, known as ‘Guides’, charge for this privilege. These fees have made the zero-population planet one of the richest per capita.

      Orbital Period: 1 Earth Year
      Radius: 6028 km
      Day Length: 18.8 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.0 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -10 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.9 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Trash</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>157</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Zennadus</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Zennadus is a world of little value to the galaxy at large. While it can sustain life, it has few useful exports, meaning that only those who have the means to sustain their livelihood inhabit it. A quiet and secluded world, Zennadus is a time capsule of a planet, where human life is lived as it was hundreds of years ago.

      Orbital Period: 28.7 Earth Years
      Radius: 4949 km
      Day Length: 29 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.87 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 8 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.06 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Castle</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>158</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Mondoshawa</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A rather small and sandy planet, Mondoshawa was spared only a cursory probe examination when explorers mapped the system. It has four moons with no official names, these being simply referred to by the names of the four ancient elements. It orbits the brilliant white star Leeloo, which itself orbits %SYSTEMNAME%.

      Orbital Period: 110.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 16,622 km
      Day Length: 18.6 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Desert</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>159</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A dark asteroid of mixed carbonaceous materials.
      Radius: 42 km
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>160</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <IsAsteroid>true</IsAsteroid>
    <PlanetName>Metallic Asteroid</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A metal-rich asteroid.
      Radius: 139 km
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>161</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>true</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>MSV Khenarthi</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      The Khenarthi is a modular conveyor of unknown design, and looks much like a tent drifting through space. The surface is covered with large, crudely-drawn advertising billboards. Attempting to ping the ship results in a return transmission showing an image of a feline biped, who ‘has wares if you have coin’. A secondary transmission, poorly encrypted, makes reference to an illicit substance known only as ‘moon sugar’.

      Registry: Rawl'kha Shipping, Elsweyr
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Ship</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>162</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Zorah Magdaros</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Zorah Magdaros is a huge, rocky terrestrial planet that is home to some of the galaxy’s largest volcanoes and a number of valuable minerals. Despite its size, the gravitational interference from its moon Nergigante is causing its orbit to decay. The salarian Fifth Fleet, carrying a full complement of scientists and engineers, has been dispatched to the system in hopes of reversing the planet’s slow destruction.

      Attempts to draw Nergigante farther away have not been successful thus far, leading many to surmise that the only option is to destroy the moon itself.

      Orbital Period: 124.7 Earth Years
      Radius: 72810 km
      Day Length: 19.7 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.73 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 192 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.78 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>LavaWorld</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>163</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Mohaine</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Mohaine is a desert wasteland. The hardpan ground is bone-dry and such a brilliant white that optical shielding is needed for close approach. Officially, the planet is devoid of resources, colonization, or anything of use. Unofficially, it is the main source of a powerful narcotic known as devil grass. This unassuming plant can be easily smuggled with other agricultural products and is far less conspicuous than red sand. While humans are able to tolerate it in small doses, it is lethal to several other species and as such, has been banned from Citadel space.

      Orbital Period:1.1 Earth Years
      Radius: 4715 km
      Day Length: 24.7 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.76 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 51 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.78 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Desert</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>164</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Marluxia</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Marluxia is a largely unexplored planet that served as a staging area for the geth exodus after the conclusion of the Geth War. For the first century, it was too close to the Perseus Veil for safe exploration; several probes were detected and destroyed by the geth before retrieving any useful information. In 1898, a probe was able to pass the atmosphere, but was lost shortly after reaching the surface. A manned mission was sent by the Citadel Council in 1890, which was also successful in reaching the surface. Reported findings included a large, castle-like structure with sterile white corridors leading to everywhere and nowhere all at once.

      The last recorded transmissions from Marluxia’s exploration team seem to suggest they either went mad or completely lost their memories. Several began to refer to the structure as ‘Castle Oblivion’ and several reports on shadow creatures, or ‘Heartless’ were filed in the mission logs before contact with the planet was lost.

      Orbital Period: 352.7 Earth Years
      Radius: 8968 km
      Day Length: 67.8 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.87 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -8 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.2 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Castle</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>165</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Zamonia</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Zamonia is a largely aquatic world with a few continental landmasses. Aside from a cursory scan of the surface, there is little information available about the planet.

      A lengthy work by Dr. A. Nightingale - the ‘Encyclopedia of Marvels, Life Forms, and Other Phenomena of Zamonia and its Environs’ - discusses the planet in great detail. However, its references to an island where foodstuffs grow instead of vegetation, talking waves, invertebrate ghosts who feed on emotions, and knowledge attained by means of bacterial infection have thrown its reliability as an accurate source of information somewhat into question.

      Orbital Period: 1296.1 Earth Years
      Radius: 29,657 km
      Day Length: 12.8 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Ocean</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>166</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>Asteroid Belt Placeholder</PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>167</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Magrathea</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Magrathea is a former manufactory powerhouse in the unique industry of planet-building. Thousands of years ago, an unknown race commissioned a planet-sized supercomputer, referred to simply as ‘Deep Thought’ in the written proposal. Unfortunately, the ultimate purpose behind its construction has been forever lost to time; shortly after being placed into orbit around a star in an empty system, the artificial planet was destroyed by another unknown race in order to make way for a hyperspatial express route.

      Unable to remain solvent in the face of this massive economic disaster, Magrathea is a shell of its past self. The factories remain, but most of them have been converted to much less monumental tasks; the most notable is the manufacture of a luxury line of towels.

      Orbital Period: 1.3 Earth Years
      Radius: 8059 km
      Day Length: 1.3 Earth Years
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.86 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 67 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.88 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Factory</ImageGroup>
    <ButtonLabel>Browse towels</ButtonLabel>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>168</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Big McLargeHuge</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A planet with a name the size of the owner himself, Big McLargeHuge is where bigger truly is better. The inhabitants of Big McLargeHuge spend vasts amount of money to maintain living a luxurious, wasteful lifestyle. Due to the very wasteful and unhealthy lifestyles of the population, the planet is often written about in curricula across the galaxy to discuss the morality of such a planet.

      In recent years, there have been ongoing efforts to change the planet’s flora to an equally extra-large-sized variety.

      Orbital Period: 227 Earth Years
      Radius: 29032 km
      Day Length: 224 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.09 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 26 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.15 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>City</ImageGroup>
    <ButtonLabel>Supersize me!</ButtonLabel>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>169</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Hashmal</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A craggy world of basaltic mountains, Hashmal is wracked by constant geologic activity. Tectonic plates are constantly piling up new mountains or collapsing old ones. The planet’s surface is covered in massive rifts.

      Orbital scans show what appears to be a tower standing on one of the tallest peaks, dubbed the ‘Pharos of Ridorana’ for its luminous surface. Much like the lighthouses of ancient Earth, the foot is littered with the remains of expeditionary ships that ventured too near and crashed against the rocks. The tower itself, however, remains untouched by the chaos.

      Orbital Period: 29.7 Earth Years
      Radius: 6843 km
      Day Length: 56.7 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.2 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -116 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.1 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Rocky</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>170</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Scadrial</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Scadrial is a planet that bears the scars of terraforming on an enormous scale. Records seem to suggest that it was once pastoral and primarily agricultural. Today, the sky is red and the surface of the planet is choked with volcanic ash. A thick mist covers the land at night and most of the plants have died from the lack of light. The reasons for this purposeful destruction are unknown.

      Scadrial’s Final Empire is controlled mainly by its nobles, who themselves are under the control of the Lord Ruler and his enforcers in the Steel Ministry. The bulk of the workforce is made up of enslaved skaa, who work the land and the factories.

      TRAVEL ADVISORY: The Church of the Survivor is currently engaged in acts of civil unrest against the Final Empire. Any travelers wishing to land on Scadrial are subject to investigation by an Obligator. Those found to be aiding or abetting the rebellion will be imprisoned and their ships seized.

      Capital: Luthadel

      Orbital Period: 2.1 Earth Years
      Radius: 7820 km
      Day Length: 15.7 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Factory</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>171</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Patricia</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Patricia is a small planet covered in verdant forest and notable for the crystal clear quality of its lakes. Pyramid Lake, named for the mountain that overshadows the water, was home to an experimental facility for refueling platform design. Made of ice and biodegradable materials, these platforms would have been deployed in the outskirts of a system, far enough from the star in order to remain intact. However, by the time they were ready for mass production, a cheaper and more efficient depot design was already in widespread use across the galaxy. With no investors willing to back the project, the prototypes were sunk to the bottom of the lake and the facility was shut down.

      The semi-intact remains of several platforms can still be seen beneath the surface of the lake, and one could argue that they are more popular as a tourist attraction than they ever were as functional structures.

      Orbital Period: 2.5 Earth Years
      Radius: 4317 km
      Day Length: 23.4 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.00 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 22 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.25 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Wilderness</ImageGroup>
    <ButtonLabel>Go swimming</ButtonLabel>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>172</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>Asteroid Belt Placeholder</PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>173</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroid>true</IsAsteroid>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Metallic Asteroid</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A metal-rich asteroid.
      Radius: 47 km
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>174</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>Asteroid Belt Placeholder</PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>175</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <IsAsteroid>true</IsAsteroid>
    <PlanetName>Rocky Asteroid</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      This asteroid is unusually thicc.
      Radius: 74 km
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>176</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Hallownest</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Hallownest is an enormous planet covered in what appears to be dense forest. Instead of trees, however, the forest is completely constructed of iron and stone. Hallownest’s native inhabitants are furtive, small, and almost bug-like in appearance. Their society is ruled by a being known simply as the Pale King.

      The salarians have expressed interest in elevating the species, but a virulent outbreak of infection has made it impossible to establish contact at this time.

      Orbital Period: 63.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 11,867 km
      Day Length: 69.7 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 3.12 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 21 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.1 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Wilderness</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>177</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Incubuso</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Incubuso is a world with a constant thin cloud cover that perpetually dims the surface, limiting the diversity of flora and fauna. The majority of the planet is a bog filled with trees that are capable of surviving in very low light conditions due to their extra-large leaves.

      Only four recorded surface expeditions on Incubuso have ever taken place. All ended in catastrophe when the expedition teams commited suicide weeks after landing. The limited data collected by these four teams indicate the local plant life has some form of defense mechanism that can induce nightmare-like hallucinations lasting for several days at a time.

      Orbital Period: 0.3 Earth Years
      Radius: 7082 km
      Day Length: 0.3 Earth Years
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.40 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 20 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.75 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Swamp</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>178</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Thynome</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Thynome is a standard hydrogen-helium gas giant. It has no remarkable features and contains nothing useful for mining.

      Scans of the micro-debris in the planet’s orbit indicates there has been traffic in the area recently; however, no ships or stations show up on scans. It is possible that a cloaked ship or station is nearby.

      Orbital Period: 36.0 Earth Years
      Radius: 56,621 km
      Day Length: 13.6 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Sky</ImageGroup>
    <NotPlayable>true</NotPlayable>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>179</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Var Hastra</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Sitting a comfortable 1500 kilometers above the uninhabited planet of the same name, Var Hastra’s station is the mining hub of the %SYSTEMNAME% system. Hundreds of asteroids of varying sizes orbit the planet, which are broken down and fed into the processing plants aboard the station.

      Unusable materials, manufacturing byproducts, and other waste are bundled up into capsules and regularly launched directly at the planet. These capsules burn up in the atmosphere, keeping the debris around Var Hastra to a minimum.

      Station Owner: Gunant Breh
      Orbital Period: 94.5 Earth Years
      Radius: 3379 km
      Day Length: 68.3 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>SpaceStation</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>180</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>Asteroid Belt Placeholder</PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>181</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <IsAsteroid>true</IsAsteroid>
    <PlanetName>Fragmented Asteroid</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      This asteroid appears to be a piece of a larger planet that was blasted away by firepower of unimaginable magnitude. Debris litters the area around it. Ships with high-grade sensor packages can pick up a weak, intermittent transmission that one ship log describes as ‘millions of voices crying out in terror.’
      Radius: 71 km
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>182</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>Asteroid Belt Placeholder</PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>183</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Kaamo</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Kaamo is a bland, desolate planet with several minor settlements along the equator. The settlements grow crops to help sustain Kaamo’s only source of income: the Kaamo Club, a space station orbiting the planet. Known for being a lightly policed retreat, it attracts some of the seediest beings in the %SYSTEMNAME% system.

      The ownership has recently changed to a human named Keith T. Maxwell, who appears to be turning the club into a more respectable establishment.

      Orbital Period: 2.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 7301 km
      Day Length: 47.2 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.00 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 29 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.1 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>SpaceStation</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>184</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Typhon</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Millennia ago, Typhon was an advanced research world that often led the way in developing innovative new technologies to the benefit of the wider galaxy. The Interstellar Manufacturing Corporation, the owners of the planet, eventually started expanding into weapons development. In the decades that followed, the IMC developed a prototype of a class of weapon they dubbed the Fold Weapon, which had unmatched destructive power. In the first test of the weapon, the only natural satellite of Typhon, Orthros, was destroyed.

      The galaxy at large saw the destructive potential of this weapon and moved to neutralize the threat before the weapon was completed. The prototype weapon misfired when the IMC used it for planetary defense, ripping the planet apart and killing its entire population when the atmosphere dissipated into space due to loss of sufficient gravity.

      Orbital Period: 0.4 Earth Years
      Radius: 9593 km
      Day Length: 19.4 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.03 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -60 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.35 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>FoldWeapon</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>185</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Smokey’s Kingdom</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Smokey’s Kingdom is a recently overthrown human settlement colony, originally named USFS Outpost 2. The planet was colonized in 2162 as a resource mill for human agriculture and other natural resources, such as wood, for export to the general %CLUSTERNAME% area. Due to significant economic dependency on these exports, great care was taken to ensure the supply chain was not disrupted.

      An unfortunate camping accident in the Payette Forest led to a wildfire that burned down 44% of the planet’s forest and crippled the local economy. A local resident named Smokey rallied the local residents to pressure the planetary government into punishing the ones who destroyed their homes, businesses, and families. After months of government inaction, Smokey eventually took matters into his own hands and overthrew the planetary government through well-coordinated riots across the backwater world.

      The citizens now live under the strict dictatorship of Smokey, where any use of fire is grounds for execution.

      Orbital Period: 1.03 Earth Years
      Radius: 4593 km
      Day Length: 23.4 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.02 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 25 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.0 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Smokey</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>186</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Pandora</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Pandora is a wild and untamed world. Much of it is covered by snow or sand deserts. Though there are several settlements and a basic planetary society, its real galactic significance lies in Helios, the enormous space station in high orbit. The station serves as headquarters for Hyperion Corporation, allowing them to oversee their vast iridium mining operations on the surface.

      Orbital Period: 67.3 Earth Years
      Radius: 5,220 km
      Day Length: 32.5 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.97 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -1 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.55 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>SpaceStation</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>187</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Amygdala</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Amygdala is a small world veiled by a layer of spidery clouds. Under the brute force of winds from the star Oedon, the atmosphere of the planet is slowly stripping away. Amygdala has one large moon spiraling into a decaying orbit. Its blood-red surface fills most of the sky when viewed from the surface of the planet.

      Orbital Period: 162.1 Earth Years
      Radius: 45,145 km
      Day Length: 12.8 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Generic</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>188</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>true</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Ishimura</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>This space station is floating dead in space and appears to have been torn apart by massive arms. Getting too close overwhelms comms with desperate whispers to ‘make us whole again’. In addition, many crew members on these ships have discovered graffiti scrawled on nearby surfaces, always a double-helix shape and usually in blood, with absolutely no memory of its significance or how it got there.</PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Ship</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>189</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Verdure</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Verdure is a world long ravaged by a war between the local dominant species, known as Guardians, and their machine counterparts, the Reploids. Due to the population’s primitive technology, they are unable to leave Verdure’s orbit, and the Citadel Council has forbidden any interference or communication with the planet.

      Observation over hundreds of years has revealed several planetary wars that significantly curtailed the population. A fairly stable government led by a group known as the Sage Trinity has kept the peace for nearly 200 years due to the forced merging of Reploids and Guardians.

      Orbital Period: 234.7 Earth Years
      Radius: 69,833 km
      Day Length: 234.7 Earth Years
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Generic</ImageGroup>
    <NotPlayable>true</NotPlayable>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>190</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Thou Fan</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Thou Fan is an insular world, cut off from the affairs of the galaxy at large. Accidental contact was made several thousand years ago when the crew of the courier ship Spirit Monk lost control and crash-landed on the surface. Its logs indicate that Thou Fan is dominated by the dynastic Jade Empire. Further notes mention a power struggle and a group known as the Lotus Assassins, but these appear to have been tampered with.

      The Spirit Monk was found floating adrift several years after its reported disappearance; no one was still alive on board. Upon inspection, the ship contained several additional skeletons that could not be matched to the crew manifest. Most suspect that the Emperor may have repaired the Spirit Monk with the intent of using it to banish his enemies.

      Orbital Period: 64.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 5198 km
      Day Length: 4.2 Earth Years
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.23 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 27 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.55 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Generic</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>191</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Capulus</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A planet with a very dense core, Capulus has one of the strongest magnetic fields in the Milky Way. Due to the strong interference from this field, most ships in the vicinity of the planet must limit their energy usage or risk electrical malfunctions. Because of this, captains usually opt to disengage FTL when passing through the system.

      The planet also possesses an extremely powerful gravity field, which had earned Capulus its nickname ‘graveyard planet’, as its misleading size can easily bait ships into a death trap. Over the past 15,000 years there have been a recorded 455 ships lost to the planet.

      Several thousand years ago, a witty but ailing salarian force used the planet as a trap to decimate their turian pursuers.

      Orbital Period: 664.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 26198 km
      Day Length: 664.8 Earth Years
      Atmospheric Pressure: 16.5 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 96 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 189 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Rocky</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>192</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Skeldon</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Skeldon is an uninhabited wasteland. The surface is a mix of sand desert encircling the equator and brush deserts flanking it at both poles. In the area between these deserts lies the only hospitable area; however, due to the harsh climate and limited resources of the planet, a logical conclusion is that nobody has ever chosen to live there.

      Orbital Period: 2.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 4453 km
      Day Length: 32 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.2 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 45 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.1 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Desert</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>193</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Desolo</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Desolo is a barren planet with an extremely fast day/night cycle of only one Earth minute. Landing on the planet is difficult due to this phenomena; however, this poses little concern, as there is nearly nothing on Desolo worth landing for. Active scans from satellites indicate a powered tether network that crosses the surface and appears to go into the subterranean areas of the planet. The question of who could have successfully landed on the planet and begun setting up a base remains unanswered.

      Due to the high rotational velocity and relatively low gravity of the planet, objects not firmly anchored to the ground are liable to be ejected from the planet’s surface. There appears to be multiple exploratory rover vehicles stuck in geosynchronous orbit with Desolo. It is likely that the drivers of the vehicles lay somewhere on the surface of the planet, unable to return to their previously built tether network before suffocation set in.

      Orbital Period: 26 Earth Minutes
      Radius: 55 km
      Day Length: 1 Earth Minute
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.01 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -55 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.25 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Barren</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>194</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Watchpoint Gibraltar</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      One of many former bases of the salarian vigilante group Overwatch, Watchpoint Gibraltar now drifts through space as a relic of years gone by. Outfitted with multiple interstellar missile launch sites, the planet was at one point considered the defense force of the %SYSTEMNAME% system.

      After decades of the group maintaining peace in the region, multiple pieces of evidence detailing some of their more brutal covert operations was leaked, causing the Salarian Union to launch an investigation. The leadership of the Overwatch group were unable to come to terms with one another, eventually leading to a skirmish that left most of the members dead. Those that remained destroyed the evidence and fled.

      Orbital Distance: 77,500 km
      Orbital Period: 3.8 Earth Days
      Radius: 4113 km
      Day Length: 4.5 Earth Days
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.0 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 24 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.88 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Ocean</ImageGroup>
    <ButtonLabel>Prepare to attack</ButtonLabel>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>195</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Sargasso</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Sargasso is a gas giant composed mostly of oxygen and hydrogen, making it an ideal planet for gas mining. The Sargasso Space Station, run by Lord O’Donnell, sits in geosynchronous orbit around the planet and makes significant revenue selling the natural hydrogen to various parts of the galaxy. Their biggest client, Space Dynamics of Corneria, is famous for developing the G-Diffuser systems, which are built with only 100% pure Sargasso hydrogen.

      Orbital Period: 1.4 Earth Years
      Radius: 6302 km
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>SpaceStation</ImageGroup>
    <NotPlayable>true</NotPlayable>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>196</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Electopia</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A terrestrial world of average size, Electopia is driven by technology and nearly everything is connected to the planetary network. Highly advanced AIs are allowed to freely roam on this network; however, per Citadel Council rules, they are restrained by extreme safeguards at the edge nodes that prevent them from transitioning to the extranet.

      Nearly all citizens of Electopia have a digital assistant AI that assists with their day-to-day lives and provides companionship. A terrorist organization known as World Three has recently introduced viruses onto the network in an attempt to corrupt or destroy these assistants and actively sabotage connected devices. A high-profile fire that broke out at the leading AI research facility SciLab is thought to have been started by an operator working for World Three.

      Orbital Distance: 14.3 AU
      Orbital Period: 60.6 Earth Years
      Radius: 5471 km
      Day Length: 66.7 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.83 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 24 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.79 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>City</ImageGroup>
    <ButtonLabel>Install NetNavi app</ButtonLabel>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>197</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Altea</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Altea is a large, terrestrial world and was the seat of King Alfor at the height of his power. A peaceful and learned people, the Alteans had keen interest in science, diplomacy, and technological advancement. Unfortunately, a large-scale scientific experiment in collaboration with the Galra caused unimaginable destruction and their alliance was broken. Zarkon, now styling himself Emperor, betrayed King Alfor and turned his fleets on Altea. The combined firepower of his capital ships devastated the planet.

      Once verdant and thriving, Altea is now devoid of life. Magma storms erupt continuously from the shattered core. The planet is surrounded by a ring system of its own rubble as it slowly breaks into pieces in the aftermath of the destruction. The Alteans and Galra themselves have long since gone extinct.

      Orbital Period: 128.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 68,714 km
      Day Length: 17.5 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>LavaWorld</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>198</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>Asteroid Belt Placeholder</PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>199</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroid>true</IsAsteroid>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Pufferfish Asteroids</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Asteroids in the vicinity bear marks of high-heat weaponry impacts. Sections of melted rock have formed spears pointing outward from their surfaces, an appearance that gave the asteroid cluster its name. The shifting gravity in this area makes travel extremely dangerous. A single asteroid tumbling into the path of a ship can puncture its hull without triggering the kinetic shielding.

      Radius: 83 km
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>200</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Ichijouji</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Ichijouji is a planet where no intelligent being ever goes, and those that do never leave. Inhabitants are forcibly fitted with Dark Ring devices around their necks and arms; the devices compel the wearer to fully succumb to the control of Ken Ichijouji, the planet’s leader. The Dark Rings operate within a certain radius of spires that broadcast control signals, and the surface of Ichijouji is covered in hundreds of such spires. Slaves are forced to build new spires, with complete planetary coverage expected in the next two years.

      New, improved devices have been found attached to several batarians traveling within the system. These devices, dubbed Dark Spirals, appear to have stronger mind control elements and are more dangerous to remove. Most notably, they apparently do not need to be within range of a control spire. These upgrades, combined with the spire expansion rate on Ichijouji, have led several species to declare the planet a threat to the galaxy at large.

      The Citadel Council has secretly authorized a complete orbital bombardment of the planet to prevent the spread of such mind control devices, which is expected to be conducted within the next 60 days.

      Orbital Period: 2.3 Earth Years
      Radius: 7377 km
      Day Length: 53.6 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.64 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 32 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.88 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Spikes</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>201</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Haven</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Described as a deadly paradise, Haven is a largely uninhabited planet. At first approach, the temperate air, lush vegetation, and inviting glow make it feel like a sanctuary. But the planet is rich with disarming dangers that have lured more than one prospector from their prize and lulled even the most objective explorer from their quest.

      The first settlers to make landfall on Haven reported a bizarre psychological pull that drove them to the surface. Expeditionary studies show that Haven’s thriving plant life actually developed a pheromone-based attraction mechanism designed to lure prey down to the surface, where they would be consumed and circulated into the system.

      Orbital Period: 1.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 5443 km
      Day Length: 39.1 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.89 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 26 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.82 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Generic</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>202</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Ashar</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Ashar's catastrophic geothermal activity results in brutal surface temperature, flowing magma, and falling ash. Due to the harsh environment, Ashar has a reputation of being a hideout for outlaws in the %CLUSTERNAME%. Being caught exposed on the surface is nearly a guaranteed deathtrap; if the outlaws don’t kill you, the firestorms that sweep the surface surely will.

      No government has outlaws valuable enough on Ashar to justify capturing the planet. Some even see it as a sort of ‘planetary arrest’, one that prevents them from leaving the surface.

      Orbital Period: 20.6 Earth Years
      Radius: 7677 km
      Day Length: 62.3 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.35 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 49 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.39 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>LavaWorld</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>203</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Famfrit</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Famfrit is an ice dwarf world, its surface composed almost entirely of frozen water. Solar winds stir the dark cloud cover into a roiling mass. An unusually large and beautiful ring of ice crystals orbits the planet, the result of an asteroid impact that shattered the surface and threw a great deal of melted water into the atmosphere. The rings will completely decay in a few thousand years. Nevertheless, they remain a popular subject in the art forms of several species.

      Orbital Period: 272.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 3111 km
      Day Length: 23.9 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.00 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -188 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.09 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Ice</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>204</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Tundria</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Tundria is a harsh ice planet with frigid temperatures, low gravity, and a thin atmosphere. Towers of frozen gas tower above cryovolcanoes that erupted in the wake of recent tectonic activity. Notable for its malodorous methane pools and towering icy ridges, only the hardiest and craziest will survive.

      On the surface is a ghost town named The Dredger, centered around a device of the same name. The device is designed to reach below the planet’s icy crust and provide access to valuable element zero and sulphur deposits. This machine and its town appear to have been abandoned; however, the cause is unknown.

      Radius: 4077 km
      Day Length: 34.6 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.69 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -19 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.75 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Ice</ImageGroup>
    <ButtonLabel>Bring sweater</ButtonLabel>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>205</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>true</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Spaceball II</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Spaceball II is the new capital ship of the planet Spaceball, brought into service after the destruction of Spaceball I over Druidia. The ship was constructed to be more resilient than the first one by removing the self destruct button, installing more seatbelts, and transforming into a ninja for space combat, instead of a maid. Additionally, it has been outfitted with anti-Winnebago railguns.

      The ship appears to have malfunctioning HyperJets and is stuck floating adrift. It also appears to be mostly powered down; something must have gone catastrophically wrong aboard.

      Registry: Dark Helmet Jr.
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Ship</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>206</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Necrom</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Necrom is a cold planet with low gravity and a thin atmosphere, known for its chimney-like flora which emit thick, toxic fog. Areas of the planet are covered in mushroom forests as tall as skyscrapers, complete with phosphorescent lamps that pour light into the winding ‘streets’ below during the night.

      Rock formations that appear to be unnatural dot the surface. Some groups on the extranet theorize that these are the tombs for the leaders of the race that inhabited the planet many millennia ago.

      Orbital Period: 107.3 Earth Years
      Radius: 4077 km
      Day Length: 34.6 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.79 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -6 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.7 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Generic</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>207</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Myotis</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Myotis is a seemingly inhabitable planet, with oceans, continents, and plant life visible from space. Upon landing, however, the planet ensnares its victims via a thin layer of fog that emanates from beneath the oceans and covers the surface of the planet. This fog causes intense and often fatal hallucinations in victims of all species.

      Survivors of the hallucinogenic fog detailed their findings in a book titled ‘The Dark Ocean’. Excerpts describe the victims roaming on a beach next to a cold, colorless dark ocean, permeated both physically and psychologically. After being near this ocean for just a few minutes, each survivor describes vivid and intense manifestations of their fears and nightmares. According to the book, the only successful attempts at rescue required tranquilizing the individual before a subsequent emergency evacuation from the planet's surface.

      Those unlucky enough to succumb to these projections still lie on the planet’s surface and can be seen with orbital imaging equipment; however, no ocean matching the book’s descriptions can be found.

      Orbital Period: 1013.7.1 Earth Years
      Radius: 17,988 km
      Day Length: 19.2 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Nightmare</ImageGroup>
    <ButtonLabel>Be courageous</ButtonLabel>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>208</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Harwood</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Harwood is a medium-sized world maintained by a group of individuals representing each race of species that inhabits it. The planet is run on the idea of living a fulfilling life with less dependence on technology; as such, most of the technology used on the planet is based around that of early-2000s Earth.

      The basic unit of population is a family, each owning a plot of land they are able to use as they see fit, as long as it is in line with the planet’s charter. Due to the very large emphasis on familial bonds, the bulk of the population on Harwood is directly descended from the original founders and most never leave the planet.

      Original Human Representative: Bud Harwood
      Population: 1.2 Million
      Radius: 8198 km
      Day Length: 59.7 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.81 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 21 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.88 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Farm</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>209</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>Asteroid Belt Placeholder</PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>210</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Edmonton</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Edmonton is a medium-size hybrid rural and city world. Between nearly all inhabited areas of the planet are various uninhabited areas such as small ranches, prairies, forested area, or wild grassland. The inhabited areas are often higher-technology constructs, leading to a visible checkerboard of tech and nature that crosses significant parts of the planet.

      Due to this, the unit of distance on the planet is simply called a ‘farm’. A restaurant is not 20 kilometers or 12 miles away - it is 10 farms away. The pervasiveness of this unit of measurement has led to the formal introduction of it into the galactic unit of measurements standards group.

      Orbital Period: 85.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 11,539 km
      Day Length: 15 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.0 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 16 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.07 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Farm</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>211</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <IsAsteroid>true</IsAsteroid>
    <PlanetName>Rocky Asteroid</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A metal-rich asteroid.
      Radius: 118 km
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>212</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Gentek Lab III</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Gentek is a recently colonized world, renamed from its original name of  Redlight. Not much is known about the planet due to the extreme defensive measures deployed on and around the planet. It has been rumored that the Alliance forced their Blackwatch division to relocate from Earth due to the previous biological disasters that occurred at original test sites Hope Idaho and Two Bluff Arizona, and the recent failures in containment of the Mercer virus in New York Zero.

      Lab III is the implementation lab of Gentek. Most ships that enter Gentek airspace never leave.

      Orbital Distance: 0.8 AU
      Orbital Period: 0.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 4404 km
      Day Length: 53.8 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.98 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 31 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.1G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Laboratory</ImageGroup>
    <ButtonLabel>Infiltrate</ButtonLabel>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>213</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Witchyworld</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Witchyworld is a run-down, low quality theme park world run by Grunty Winkybunion, who also owns the mega-conglomerate Grunty Industries. The theme park component of the world has been continuously losing money due to the steep decline of visitors following the unsanitary food preparation documentary.

      The following information is available in the official Witchyworld attraction brochure:

      Experience a world of amazing delights, where most of them won’t make you lose your sight! Yes, you're right - I'm rather proud! My theme park makes me stand out from the crowd!

      THE INFERNO(TM)*
      Experience a skin-boiling sensation as you try to climb to the top of THE INFERNO(TM)! Water is sold in bundles of 5 for 600 credits each. Will you beat the heat, or will we have to toss your body into the lava below to meet safety inspections?

      SPACE ZONE(TM)**
      Enjoy the cosmos in the SPACE ZONE! Ride our multi-tiered space elevator to Mecha Saturn, hold in your guts with the SAUCER OF PERIL(TM), or enjoy a raucous round of bumper cars against the local captive species in the DODGEM DOME!

      DIVE OF DEATH(TM)
      A wondrous view from hundreds of meters in the sky, with no way down! What’s that below? A four foot deep swimming pool? Test your diving skills with the DIVE OF DEATH! Will you survive the dive?

      MADAME’S FORTUNE TELLING
      The witch herself will tell you your fortune! For a small fee, I, Gruntilda Winkybunion, will hold your fate in my hands! Please empty your pockets upon entering my tent, and do not discuss your fate with others.

      * Premium ticketholders only
      ** Some attractions require premium tickets

      Food may not be removed from the park premises. All purchased food must be eaten or discarded while within park premises.

      Orbital Period: 0.9 Earth Years
      Radius: 6506 km
      Day Length: 0.5 Earth Days
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.99 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 16 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.1 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>ThemePark</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>214</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Jersey’s Torment</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A stormy water world that carries a twisted history, Jersey’s Torment is named after the initial failed colonization attempt conducted by a turian known as Jersey. The original plan involved dropping ships onto the ocean’s surface to probe the ocean floor for aquatic life and resources.

      While he was successful in finding ways to sustain life aboard a floating ship, Jersey became increasingly agitated by isolation after his communications equipment ceased to work. A supply frigate later discovered the remains of his ship strewn over the planet’s watery surface, devoid of any signs of attack or struggle. Recovery of Jersey’s journal indicates the isolation drove him to complete insanity; however, the last dated entry and the ship’s last recorded activity have a discrepancy of several months.

      The remains of Jersey’s ship, along with several other colony ships, are the only noteworthy items on the ocean’s surface.

      Orbital Period: 41.5 Earth Years
      Radius: 5198 km
      Day Length: 44 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.88 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 14 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.89 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>WaterWorld</ImageGroup>
    <NotPlayable>true</NotPlayable>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>215</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Click Clock</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A world lost in time, Click Clock is covered entirely by the Click Clock Woods. The woods are known to warp the sense of time of those who land on the planet, creating an amnesia-like effect. The effect seems to only go both fast and slow, affecting each individual differently; some believe time has advanced much farther than it has, while the rest think very little has passed.

      For this reason the Citadel Council has marked Click Clock as an off-limits world; however, this has not dissuaded those who wish to live the rest of their lives in this warped sense of time.

      Orbital Distance: 22.2 AU
      Orbital Period: 117.7 Earth Years
      Radius: 11,621 km
      Day Length: 62.0  Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.88 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 25 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.9 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Wilderness</ImageGroup>
    <NotPlayable>true</NotPlayable>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>216</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>Asteroid Belt Placeholder</PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>217</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <IsAsteroid>true</IsAsteroid>
    <PlanetName>Carbonaceous Asteroid</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A dark asteroid of mixed carbonaceous materials. This asteroid shows sign of impact by weapons fire.
      Radius: 63 km
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>218</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Pallet</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Pallet is a quiet, mostly uninhabited planet teeming with different types of wildlife. While of little value to the galaxy at large, the professor at the planet’s only learning institution has been cataloguing all species on the planet. A recently completed device intended to aid in the cataloguing of his planet’s species has led to the invention of the Galactic Dex(TM).

      This device has been licensed to the Citadel Council for use during official expeditions to uncharted worlds, which will greatly speed up the identification of various species on unknown planets.

      Orbital Period: 0.7 Earth Years
      Radius: 7593 km
      Day Length: 18.1 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.12 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 27 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.2 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Wilderness</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>219</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Cinnabar</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Cinnabar is an abandoned ocean world that was once home to state-of- the-art genetic engineering facilities. Originally chosen for its small land mass on the surface, Cinnabar was designed to keep those on the surface grounded, rather than keeping outsiders out. Due to limited land mass, both the living quarters and laboratory were housed in the same location, named Cinnabar Mansion.

      Historical information about this ‘mansion’ is sparse. It appears there was some catastrophic failure with a specimen containment system, leading to the destruction of most of the facility. Several years later, an undersea volcano erupted, wiping away most of the evidence of any activity on the planet.

      Orbital Period: 2.9 Earth Years
      Radius: 5160 km
      Day Length: 38.7 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.83 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 16 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.8 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Ocean</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>220</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Pewter</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Pewter is a mountainous planet, covered in uneven craggy folds that make planetary colonization difficult. The planet’s largest mountain, Mount Moon, has a large cave system woven through the base that extends several dozen kilometers beneath the surface. Exploration has led to discovery of a large underground network of tunnels that cover the majority of the planet’s surface.

      Archeologists from around the galaxy practice their spelunking skills by exploring the depths of these caverns. When artifacts of life are retrieved, they are entered into the galaxy-renowned Pewter City historical record.

      Orbital Period: 9.9 Earth Years
      Radius: 11541 km
      Day Length: 16.2 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Rocky</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>221</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Viridian</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Viridian is a seemingly peaceful planet, notable for having some of the best learning institutions in the %SYSTEMNAME% system. The majority of the planet is covered in dense forest that is easy to get lost in.

      Multiple board members of the Viridian City academy have reported suspicious monetary activity surrounding the president of the institution, Giovanni. An investigation is currently underway.

      Orbital Period: 5.6 Earth Years
      Radius: 21481 km
      Day Length: 21.3 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Wilderness</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>222</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>Asteroid Belt Placeholder</PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>223</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>true</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>MSV New York</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      The MSV New York is a mid-size conveyor of human design, named after one of the largest metropolitan areas of Earth. The ship is famously known around the galaxy as  a traveling tourist trap, bringing many New York cultural sensations to distant worlds.

      This ship appears to be in a low-power state; most systems are powered down and the pizza has long gone cold. Visual scans show a large poster-sized sticker near the rear thrusters, with the faded phrase "We brake for nobody".

      Registry: Traveling Rays, Earth
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Ship</ImageGroup>
    <ButtonLabel>Get free pizza</ButtonLabel>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>224</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Fuchsia</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Fuchsia, aptly named after its environment’s ugly haze, is an uninhabited world due to the thick layer of poisonous gas that swirls in the planet’s winds. At night, the toxic atmosphere is thick enough that even the reflection of light from other planets in the system is unable to pierce the fog.

      In a move that leaves investors worried and defies all logic, a company named Safari Zone is attempting to set up a zoo on the planet’s surface. This zoo would show off the planet’s hardiest creatures that are able to survive the poisonous air.

      Orbital Period: 284.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 57,948 km
      Day Length: 10.8 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Sky</ImageGroup>
    <NotPlayable>true</NotPlayable>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>225</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Cerulean</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Named after the vast expanses of ocean that cover most of the surface, Cerulean is an aquamarine paradise. Tourism to the depths of its deep oceans is one of the most common forms of commerce on the planet. Along the equator of the planet is a complete boardwalk with attached docks that encircle the planet, which uses stabilization technology based on mass effect fields. The boardwalk enables various recreational activities, such as biking, with some inhabitants making it their life goal to complete an entire circling of the planet.

      Buildings float on the surface of the ocean, and are typically anchored to the boardwalk. Various roaming marinas provide a secluded yet accessible stay on Cerulean. The capital of the planet, Cerulean City, is considered one of the most romantic places in the galaxy.

      Orbital Period: 1930.3 Earth Years
      Radius: 7979 km
      Day Length: 22.4 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.07 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 22 Celsius
      Surface Gravity 1.2 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>WaterWorld</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>226</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Lavender</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Lavender is a mostly barren planet, described by thousands of visitors as a haunted world. Six ancient buildings from several hundred thousand years ago are the only notable landmarks on the surface. Inside these towers are hundreds of stone tablets with indiscernible text printed on each of them, each different from the next.

      Extended stays lead to increasing paranoia for nearly all species who grace the planet’s surface. Perhaps the lack of significant vegetation and water on the planet is actually a good omen.

      Orbital Period: 255 Earth Years
      Radius: 12987 km
      Day Length: 16.3 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Spire</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>227</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>Asteroid Belt Placeholder</PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Asteroid</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>228</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Saffron</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      As a world for the technological elite, Saffron has found itself in a rather unusual situation: a significant part of the population is part of a planetary cult. The leader of this cult, known as Sabrina, claims to have psychic powers allowing her to perform advanced telekinetic techniques that even outmatch biotics. Sabrina is rarely found without a girl that looks like a younger version of herself.

      The planet is mostly run in the shadows by this cult. The majority of the board members for Silph, the most well-known company based on Saffron, are also part of the cult’s senior leadership. The Citadel Council is closely monitoring the spread of the cult, ensuring its containment within the borders of Saffron.

      Orbital Period: 42.3 Earth Years
      Radius: 4906 km
      Day Length: 52.0 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.82 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 14 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.8 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>City</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>229</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Celadon</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Celedon is one of the largest commerce hubs in the galaxy. Nearly the entire surface of the planet is covered by warehouses, all belonging to the Celadon City company. Founded hundreds of years ago, Celadon City was a warehousing company that took the galaxy by storm. With low prices and fast shipping to all areas in Council-controlled space, many less adaptive shipping companies fell by the wayside as Celadon City rose to its current elite status.

      In 2170 it merged with the Earth mega-conglomerate Amazon, leading to 48-hour free shipping to anywhere within 200 light years of a mass relay in Council space.

      Orbital Period: 0.5 Earth Years
      Radius: 4839 km
      Day Length: 54 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.34 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 33 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.3 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Factory</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>230</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Mustafar</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Mustafar was once a scorching lava world many tens of thousands of years ago, during which it was heavily mined for various resources. Cooling of the planet’s core has led to most lava flows hardening into basalt formations that form elegant patterns across the planet’s surface.

      Historical records indicate that Mustafar was the turning point of an ancient galactic civil war, where the opposing party was soundly crushed and defeated. Today it lies empty and barren, with little to no value to its visitors.

      Orbital Period: 31.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 73,733 km
      Day Length: 16.7 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Rocky</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>231</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Dagobah</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Largely overlooked by the races of the Citadel, Dagobah is one of the only habitable planets in the %CLUSTERNAME%. A cloudy and swampy world of dense foliage, the countless living things of all sizes, including reptiles, amphibians, and swarming insects, fill its environs with a hum of constant noise.

      Explorers landing on the planet often report hallucinations of increasing intensity after being on the surface for more than a few days, which has effectively warded off any long-term colonization of the planet.

      Orbital Period: 0.6 Earth Years
      Radius: 3839 km
      Day Length: 16 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.2 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 19 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.1 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Swamp</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>232</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Pantsless</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Pantless is a large rock world with an unusually thin atmosphere of methane, likely caused by uncovered emissions from the surface. The world’s crust contains extensive deposits of uranium. With a total mass more than four times that of Earth, Pantsless should have a significantly thicker atmosphere. It also features an unusual crater on the lower half, effectively splitting the planet into two ‘limbs’. This unusual feature has flagged it as worthy of scientific investigation.

      Orbital Period: 297.4 Earth Years
      Radius: 8927 km
      Day Length: 36.0 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.06 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -174 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 2.8 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Rocky</ImageGroup>
    <ButtonLabel>Sigh…</ButtonLabel>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <!-- Start of Bring Down The Sky -->
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>0</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <IsAsteroid>false</IsAsteroid>
    <DLC>UNC</DLC>
    <PlanetName>Terra Nova</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Terra Nova was one of the Class-1 colonization prospects discovered by the first wave of Alliance surveys in 2150. It was the second human extrasolar colony, and the first beyond the Charon Mass Relay. It currently has the highest population of any Alliance colony.

      Though banded by a harsh equatorial desert, areas closer to the poles are temperate. The pace of development was modest until extensive deposits of platinum were discovered in the 2170s. This rare metal, required in the clean-burning hydrogen fuel cells that power private vehicles, attracted a "platinum rush" of immigrants and investment from throughout Alliance space. In the past twelve years, Terra Nova has seen a 30% rise in population, and growth does not appear to be slowing.

      Colony Founded: 2152
      Population: 4.4 million
      Capital: Scott

      Orbital Period: 1.5 Earth Years
      Radius: 5261 km
      Day Length: 37.3 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.91 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 56 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.95 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>1</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <IsAsteroid>false</IsAsteroid>
    <DLC>UNC</DLC>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid X57</PlanetName>
    <PlanetName2>Shard IV of Corda</PlanetName2>
    <PlanetDescription>
      %PLANETNAME% is one of six pieces being brought back together in a state of the art attempt to reconstruct the shattered planet of Corda. Destroyed 16 years ago by an unknown force that escaped through the mass relay network, the Shards of Corda have been drifting apart for years. The recent reconstruction initiative two years ago led to the installation of fusion torches on the surface of the shards in an attempt to bring them to a single rendezvous point, where work on the construction of the planetary core can begin.

      %PLANETNAME% is currently off course and is on a potential collision course with a nearby human colony.  Impact with the colony will cause catastrophic destruction to the colony and ensure that Corda is never rebuilt.
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>PlanetDestruction</ImageGroup>
    <ButtonLabel>Save two planets</ButtonLabel>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>2</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <IsAsteroid>false</IsAsteroid>
    <DLC>UNC</DLC>
    <PlanetName>Coruscant</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Coruscant is an ecumenopolis - a city covered planet - notable for its political influence on Citadel Council affairs. Located conveniently along many trade routes, Coruscant is one of the most densely populated worlds in the Milky Way. It is a pioneer planet in new energy exploration as well as environmental control systems, and is where a significant portion of Council governance is actually performed behind the scenes.

      Due to the limited size of the Citadel and the high cost of living, Coruscant is typically seen as an acceptable second place for political work in Council space. High rising towers allow the politically elite to have a view of the city for tens of kilometers; the surface and sublevels of the reserved for those unable to make ends meet.

      It is estimated that the planet generates over 150 trillion credits every single day.

      Population: 1.4 trillion (estimated)
      Orbital Period: 1.1 Earth Years
      Radius: 6,120 km
      Day Length: 23.8 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>City</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>3</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <IsAsteroid>false</IsAsteroid>
    <DLC>UNC</DLC>
    <PlanetName>Delfino</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Delfino is a dry planet known for its array of ancient castles scattered about its surface. Although they have been long since abandoned, the castles have proven to be very popular archeological study, providing significant detail about their inhabitants and the lives they lived.

      Thousands of years ago, Defino was a temperate planet, hosting a wide range of biomes. A cataclysmic event occurred that caused a significant portion of the planet’s flora to die off, sending the sentient beings into a panic about how to ensure their own survival.

      The capital castle was owned by someone named Peach, and a recovered diary from this individual contained several complaints about the constant failure of her guards to provide any meaningful protection from her adversaries. The final entry detailed her plans to harness the power of the stars in an attempt to save her citizens, however if this succeeded is unknown.

      Orbital Period: 17.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 4630 km
      Day Length: 19.3 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.9 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 27 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.22 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Castle</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>4</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <IsAsteroid>false</IsAsteroid>
    <DLC>UNC</DLC>
    <PlanetName>Scuttle</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Scuttle is a lightly populated planet covered mostly by forests, with little to make it stand out. While the majority of the population lives in the seventeen official towns of the planet, a few nomadic groups are also known to exist, their membership consisting mostly of exiles from the towns. The planetary technology is limited due to very little investment from outside benefactors, leading most citizens to live a quiet lifestyle.

      Due to the hostility between some of the nomadic groups and the townships, each town has a designated ‘guardian genie’ who is tasked with protecting the town at all costs.

      Population: 62,000
      Capital: Tassel Town

      Orbital Period: 8 Earth Years
      Radius: 6332 km
      Day Length: 46.2 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.8 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 21 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.95 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Wilderness</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>5</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <IsAsteroid>false</IsAsteroid>
    <DLC>UNC</DLC>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid X57</PlanetName>
    <PlanetName2>Shard IV of Corda</PlanetName2>
    <PlanetDescription>
      %PLANETNAME% has been brought under control and is correcting its vector to the rendezvous point. Though the batarian terrorists have significantly damaged the fusion torches and set the rendezvous back several months, experts predict it can still make within the current calendar year.

      The Corda Coalition would like to thank Commander Shepard and his team aboard the SSV Normandy SR-1 for saving the shard and millions of human lives. The Coalition is planning to install a commemorative Commander Shepard statue in the capital city of Corda when the initial shard bonding is completed, expected in 2187.
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>SavedShard</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>6</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <IsAsteroid>false</IsAsteroid>
    <DLC>UNC</DLC>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid X57</PlanetName>
    <PlanetName2>Shard IV of Corda</PlanetName2>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <!-- End of BDTS -->

  <!-- Start of Pinnacle Station-->
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>0</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <IsAsteroid>false</IsAsteroid>
    <DLC>Vegas</DLC>
    <ButtonLabel>Find a seat</ButtonLabel>
    <PlanetName>Pinnacle Station</PlanetName>
    <PlanetName2>Ahern’s Crab Shack</PlanetName2>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Considered one of the finest bed and breakfasts in this area of space, %PLANETNAME% is a popular stop for visitors traveling through the area. Founded in 2160 after hanging up his life aboard the high seas, Captain Ahern opened his bed and breakfast hoping to bring his love for seafood to the masses. Featuring a system class dining experience with fresh seafood from nearby planets, it offers something for everyone.

      For adults, they have special fantasy rooms with sound proof walls, for the older folk a history museum for the cluster, and a hyper-realistic combat simulator designed for children. The staff for the combat simulator have found difficulty keeping some of the adults from usurping the leaderboards from the kids.

      Population: 452
      Radius: 940m
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Restaurant</ImageGroup>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>1</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <IsAsteroid>false</IsAsteroid>
    <DLC>Vegas</DLC>
    <PlanetName>Pinnacle Station</PlanetName>
    <PlanetName2>Ahern’s Crab Shack</PlanetName2>
    <Description>This planet is unused</Description>
    <DLC>Vegas</DLC>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>2</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <IsAsteroid>false</IsAsteroid>
    <DLC>Vegas</DLC>
    <PlanetName>Intai'sei</PlanetName>
    <PlanetName2>Oshiro</PlanetName2>
    <PlanetDescription>
      An atmosphere similar to Earth's made %PLANETNAME% an early candidate for human colonization. However, prohibitively high temperatures and an arid climate limit agricultural activities. The majority of the population of %PLANETNAME% lives near the poles where the climate is more favorable for plant life.

      Mount Celeste, a mountain near the equator, has become a tourist attraction in recent years due to the reported positive psychological effects the climb has had for its hikers. It is one of the only remarkable features of planet.

      Colony Founded: 2166
      Population: 44,000
      Capital: Madeline

      Orbital Period: 27.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 5897 km
      Day Length: 27.6 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.95 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 46 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.8 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <ImageGroup>Barren</ImageGroup>
    <ButtonLabel>Netflix and Chill</ButtonLabel>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>3</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <IsAsteroid>false</IsAsteroid>
    <DLC>Vegas</DLC>
    <PlanetName>Little house on the Prairie</PlanetName>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <!-- End of Pinnacle Station -->
</planetinfos>
