<!--
The intro text only supports 8 lines of text. If you go over this, it won’t appear.
-->
<IntroCrawlTexts>
  <CrawlText>
    One month after the devastating geth attack on the Citadel, the galactic community struggles to rebuild.

    The Asari, Turian, and Salarian races have been forced to recognize humanity's role in saving the Citadel. This ascension to power has angered many of the other races, leading to conflict in the outer region, and splinter groups within humanity itself who do not wish to cater to the other species in the galaxy.

    As tensions build, everyone waits for the spark that starts the fire...
  </CrawlText>
  <CrawlText>
    Only a select few in our galaxy have survived the cataclysm that mutated us. As one of these chosen few, you’ve been conditioned to put down these scourges of the galaxy, of which there are many.

    You are humanity’s chosen champion. You must rise to the challenge and show that you can rescue humanity, and once this is all over… you can find your own humanity again.

    This is your call to arms. Get rid of what they call...
  </CrawlText>
  <CrawlText>
    Hello there! Welcome to the galaxy of ALIENS and SPACE MAGIC! My name is UDINA! People call me the ALIEN PROF! This galaxy is inhabited by creatures called BATARIANS! And SALARIANS! For some people, ALIENS are friends. Others use them for committing war crimes against other species, like sterilization!

    Myself...I study ALIEN POLITICS as a profession.

    Shepard! Let's go!
  </CrawlText>
  <CrawlText>
    A vorcha, a batarian and a quarian are in a skycar, who's driving?






    C-Sec.
  </CrawlText>
  <CrawlText>
    In 2027, explorers on the moon of the planet Earth discovered the remains of a vehicle left there 55 years before. 81 years later, unable to contain its needs for its populations, the people of Earth expanded into the Sol system. In 2144 nuclear war broke out over the last remaining resources of Earth, leaving humanity’s future in peril.

    Then everything changed... We found that we’re just a drop in the bucket of life across the galaxy...
  </CrawlText>
  <CrawlText>
    Rudimentary creatures of blood and flesh. You may have defeated one, but we are many. Our purpose transcends your understanding.

    The pattern cannot be stopped. Your civilization has reached its apex, and now we will restore order to the galaxy. 

    You existed because we allowed it. And we ended you, because we demanded it.
  </CrawlText>
  <CrawlText>
    [Record Scratch]
    [Freeze Frame]

    Yup, that’s me. You’re probably wondering how I ended up in this situation.

    I was with a friend on this ship, and I asked to try on their N7 uniform. One unfortunate accident later, and now they think I’m Lieutenant Commander Shepard...
  </CrawlText>
  <CrawlText>
    It is a dark time for the galaxy. Although the Rebel forces were repelled, the Battle of the Citadel caused a deep rift in the leadership of the Citadel Council.
  
    Evading the weakened forces, the Geth retreated into hiding, luring the savior of the Citadel into a deadly trap.

    The evil forces begin to stir, knowing that it is now the right time to strike...
  </CrawlText>
  <CrawlText>
    Captain's Log, December 18, 2183.

    We have just come into orbit of Alchera as we attempt to root out the last Geth holdouts. The council has done nothing but brush us off, and constantly has been saying now is now the time to assign blame. They are wholly uninterested in this dire threat to our existence.

    I'm beginning to think they've dismissed my claims...
  </CrawlText>
</IntroCrawlTexts>
