<backgroundstrings>
  <childhoods>
    <childhood name="Child at heart">
      You never really grew up in your mind. You've still got your favorite Lego set on your shelf in your room on the ship. Your toys helped distract you from the rough life you lived when you were younger, and you never really grew out of that.

      Your crewmates on the SSV Normandy teased you for it sometimes, but nobody could deny the tactical awareness you've gained from your experience with toys, which were unfortunately lost with the ship.
    </childhood>
    <childhood name="Hipster">
      You were too cool for school, and you let everyone know it. You're the ultimate hipster - if someone knows what you like, it's already too mainstream. You rode the wave of cool before it was cool, but your mother didn't approve, and you were kicked out and ended up in the military.

      You became the commander of the SSV Normandy, becoming the pinnacle hipster. But that title was lost with destruction of the SSV Normandy.
    </childhood>
    <childhood name="Life of the party">
      If there was a party, you were there. You partied so hard the local news would write stories about you. Your early twenties were so much fun, or at least the pictures others took seem to indicate you had fun, because you actually can't remember most of it.

      The party ended with your death on the SSV Normandy, and you were mourned by fraternities all over Earth.
    </childhood>
    <childhood name="Imposter">
      Your original career choice was influenced by the admiration of a popular chef. Joining a space transportation company as a young self proclaimed culinary wizard trying to get your food in the door, you were bounced around from ship to ship trying to find a suitable place of work.

      It would have been devastating if anyone had learned that you actually couldn't cook. Thankfully you were mistakenly assigned to the command of the SSV Normandy, so you didn't have to cook anymore.
    </childhood>
    <childhood name="Scientist">
      You survived the quarantine of New York Zero in 2165, which claimed the lives of both of your parents and your brother. Devastated by your loss, you spent years becoming a child prodigy of the sciences to help ensure this would not happen again, leading you to join the Alliance's scientific division when you turned 18.

      Working with various scientists from other races, you helped develop a cure for the disease, and were subsequently reassigned into the military division.
    </childhood>
    <childhood name="Introvert">
      Your parents divorced when you were young, and ever since then, you've had trouble maintaining relationships with others. You found it uncomfortable to exert the energy required to hold up your end of the deal, causing many connections to others to wither away.

      You spent a lot of time on your own, becoming independent and acquiring an ability to recognize the subtle non-verbal communications of others. These skills let you understand people at a glance, a skill the Alliance took notice of.
    </childhood>
  </childhoods>
  <reputations>
    <reputation name="Rough Rider">
      A cowboy is how they used to call them back in the time before planes, your policy was shoot first and ask questions later. Known to lay down the law when necessary, you also know when to let up, and let people learn from their own mistakes. It looks like the Geth may have finally called your bluff.

      Joke's on them.
    </reputation>
    <reputation name="Terrorist">
      Your enemies cringed when they hear your name. So did your allies. You are known to be an absolutely ruthless and brutal soldier, willing to do anything to get the job done, consequences be damned.
      
      But that's all in the past. The Normandy SR-1 was destroyed, and now you're nothing but a piece of human steak on a lab table. Whoever did this to you better be ready, because your boot will be meeting their neck soon.
    </reputation>
    <reputation name="Pacifist (in name only)">
      The kindest soul that there ever was, was how someone once described you. You wouldn't hurt a fly, and you'd surely let the spider out of the house rather than smashing it.

      At least, that was what they used to think. Two years ago you became bloodthirsty, shooting up bars, med clinics, and platoons worth of Geth. The Alliance seemed almost thankful you died on the SR-1 so they didn't have to deal with you anymore.
    </reputation>
    <reputation name="Social Elite">
      You didn't need to wield guns to show your power, you had people willing to do it for you. You had friends in high places who owed you favors you intended to collect on someday, and today was that day: rebuild me. 

      You intend to visit some of these "friends" and see who's willing to pay up, and to see who's afraid of ghosts.
    </reputation>
    <reputation name="Influencer">
      I was Commander Shepard, and this was my favorite department store on Earth.

      Your advertising skills were so legendary, you were often called Billy Mays III. Merchants knew you by name even if you never stepped foot in their shop. But that legend ended when the Normandy SR-1 was destroyed.

      But you're about to start a comeback tour, this time ready to sell spaceships worth of humanity's next greatest invention: thermal clips.
    </reputation>
    <reputation name="Streamer">
      You've always been a performer; starting this "streaming" thing 5 years ago when you joined the Alliance military. The Alliance saw the following you cultivated, granting you promotions that quickly led you up the ranks, bringing many new recruits into the service. You were a bit too ambitious though, and got the Normandy SR-1 blown up in one your Geth Prank'd videos. The Alliance post humorously court-martialed you as a result.

      Your audience of 770,000 live viewers are about to see the highest technical achievement of the human race: Shepard Mark II.
    </reputation>
    <reputation name="Sombra main">
      You love having fun, but only at the expense of others. You're the background noise, making yourself known only when you make a grand entrance. You found your way into computer systems that were always touted as 'impenetrable', and technically "still are", at least according to the owners.
      
      These hacking skills have helped you evade the Alliance by hiding in plain sight, creating a perfect disguise as 'Commander Shepard'. It will be difficult to continue this cover with the Normandy-SR1 destroyed.
    </reputation> 
  </reputations>
</backgroundstrings>